(function(e){function t(t){for(var i,s,a=t[0],l=t[1],u=t[2],p=0,c=[];p<a.length;p++)s=a[p],Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(n,s)&&n[s]&&c.push(n[s][0]),n[s]=0;for(i in l)Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(l,i)&&(e[i]=l[i]);m&&m(t);while(c.length)c.shift()();return r.push.apply(r,u||[]),o()}function o(){for(var e,t=0;t<r.length;t++){for(var o=r[t],i=!0,s=1;s<o.length;s++){var a=o[s];0!==n[a]&&(i=!1)}i&&(r.splice(t--,1),e=l(l.s=o[0]))}return e}var i={},s={app:0},n={app:0},r=[];function a(e){return l.p+"js/"+({"risk-prioritization~survey":"risk-prioritization~survey","risk-prioritization":"risk-prioritization",survey:"survey"}[e]||e)+"."+{"chunk-497ef5ee":"a09ec391","risk-prioritization~survey":"8b8e0c89","risk-prioritization":"a16bff52",survey:"02ef9f66"}[e]+".js"}function l(t){if(i[t])return i[t].exports;var o=i[t]={i:t,l:!1,exports:{}};return e[t].call(o.exports,o,o.exports,l),o.l=!0,o.exports}l.e=function(e){var t=[],o={"chunk-497ef5ee":1,"risk-prioritization~survey":1,"risk-prioritization":1,survey:1};s[e]?t.push(s[e]):0!==s[e]&&o[e]&&t.push(s[e]=new Promise((function(t,o){for(var i="css/"+({"risk-prioritization~survey":"risk-prioritization~survey","risk-prioritization":"risk-prioritization",survey:"survey"}[e]||e)+"."+{"chunk-497ef5ee":"523a7900","risk-prioritization~survey":"9a648997","risk-prioritization":"2ff5fde4",survey:"53cb3f1f"}[e]+".css",n=l.p+i,r=document.getElementsByTagName("link"),a=0;a<r.length;a++){var u=r[a],p=u.getAttribute("data-href")||u.getAttribute("href");if("stylesheet"===u.rel&&(p===i||p===n))return t()}var c=document.getElementsByTagName("style");for(a=0;a<c.length;a++){u=c[a],p=u.getAttribute("data-href");if(p===i||p===n)return t()}var m=document.createElement("link");m.rel="stylesheet",m.type="text/css",m.onload=t,m.onerror=function(t){var i=t&&t.target&&t.target.src||n,r=new Error("Loading CSS chunk "+e+" failed.\n("+i+")");r.code="CSS_CHUNK_LOAD_FAILED",r.request=i,delete s[e],m.parentNode.removeChild(m),o(r)},m.href=n;var y=document.getElementsByTagName("head")[0];y.appendChild(m)})).then((function(){s[e]=0})));var i=n[e];if(0!==i)if(i)t.push(i[2]);else{var r=new Promise((function(t,o){i=n[e]=[t,o]}));t.push(i[2]=r);var u,p=document.createElement("script");p.charset="utf-8",p.timeout=120,l.nc&&p.setAttribute("nonce",l.nc),p.src=a(e);var c=new Error;u=function(t){p.onerror=p.onload=null,clearTimeout(m);var o=n[e];if(0!==o){if(o){var i=t&&("load"===t.type?"missing":t.type),s=t&&t.target&&t.target.src;c.message="Loading chunk "+e+" failed.\n("+i+": "+s+")",c.name="ChunkLoadError",c.type=i,c.request=s,o[1](c)}n[e]=void 0}};var m=setTimeout((function(){u({type:"timeout",target:p})}),12e4);p.onerror=p.onload=u,document.head.appendChild(p)}return Promise.all(t)},l.m=e,l.c=i,l.d=function(e,t,o){l.o(e,t)||Object.defineProperty(e,t,{enumerable:!0,get:o})},l.r=function(e){"undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.toStringTag&&Object.defineProperty(e,Symbol.toStringTag,{value:"Module"}),Object.defineProperty(e,"__esModule",{value:!0})},l.t=function(e,t){if(1&t&&(e=l(e)),8&t)return e;if(4&t&&"object"===typeof e&&e&&e.__esModule)return e;var o=Object.create(null);if(l.r(o),Object.defineProperty(o,"default",{enumerable:!0,value:e}),2&t&&"string"!=typeof e)for(var i in e)l.d(o,i,function(t){return e[t]}.bind(null,i));return o},l.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e["default"]}:function(){return e};return l.d(t,"a",t),t},l.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)},l.p="/app/esa/",l.oe=function(e){throw console.error(e),e};var u=window["webpackJsonp"]=window["webpackJsonp"]||[],p=u.push.bind(u);u.push=t,u=u.slice();for(var c=0;c<u.length;c++)t(u[c]);var m=p;r.push([0,"chunk-vendors"]),o()})({0:function(e,t,o){e.exports=o("cd49")},"0462":function(e,t,o){e.exports=o.p+"img/home-survey-icon.d24782f4.svg"},"16a3":function(e,t,o){"use strict";var i=o("fe4d"),s=o.n(i);s.a},"1a7b":function(e,t,o){},"21bb":function(e,t,o){"use strict";var i=o("d63f"),s=o.n(i);s.a},"283c":function(e,t,o){e.exports=o.p+"img/EAC_logo.448fdb04.svg"},"2a01":function(e,t,o){"use strict";var i=o("3ee9"),s=o.n(i);s.a},"3ee9":function(e,t,o){},"40c8":function(e,t,o){e.exports=o.p+"img/CISA_logo.7788a461.svg"},"45cd":function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('{"voterRegistrationQuestions":{"scaleQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Scale of Voter Registration Database (VRDB)","sectionId":1,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"jurisdictionOrState":{"question":"Is the database managed at the Jurisdiction or State level?","options":["Jurisdiction","State"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"jurisdictionOrState","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"scale":{"question":"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.","options":["High","Medium","Low"],"type":"dropdown","show":false,"id":"scale","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"tooltip":"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},"accessQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Access to Voter Registration Database (VRDB)","sectionId":2,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"remoteAccess":{"question":"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"remoteAccess","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"question":"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"remoteAccessNoAuth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"anyIPS":{"question":"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"anyIPS","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System","service":"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B","tooltip":"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"allowList":{"question":"Do you add IPs to the \'Allow List\'?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"allowList","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses","service":"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy","source":"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf","tooltip":"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"proximateAccess":{"question":"Is there proximate access to the system?","tooltip":"Proximate access refers to \'Bluetooth\' and \'Wifi\'.","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"proximateAccess","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"bluetooth":{"question":"Is Bluetooth enabled?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"bluetooth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wifi":{"question":"Is there WiFi access?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wifi","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wepOrWpa1":{"question":"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wepOrWpa1","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wpa2":{"question":"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wpa2","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"physicalMedia":{"question":"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"physicalMedia","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"question":"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"removableMediaPolicy","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Enact removable media policy","service":"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf","tooltip":"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"authQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Authentication","sectionId":3,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"anyAuth":{"question":"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"anyAuth","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"sfa":{"question":"Do you use single factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"sfa","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"mfa":{"question":"Do you use multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"mfa","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"tfa":{"question":"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"tfa","mitigation":"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet","source":"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf","tooltip":"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"ofa":{"question":"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"ofa","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Hardware Management","sectionId":4,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.","questions":{"patchHardware":{"question":"Do you patch the voter registration database server?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"patchHardware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"patchHardwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the server more frequently than once per election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"patchHardwareElection","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Software Management","sectionId":5,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.","questions":{"patchSoftware":{"question":"Do you patch your application software for the voter registration database?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"patchSoftware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the software more frequently than once per election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"patchSoftwareElection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"DDoS Protection","sectionId":6,"complete":false,"tooltip":"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.","questions":{"ddosProtection":{"question":"Do you have DDoS protection for your server?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"ddosProtection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Implement DDoS protection","service":"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Importance Values","sectionId":7,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"confidentiality":{"type":"slider","default":3.3,"question":"Confidentiality","id":"confidentiality","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.3,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"integrity":{"type":"slider","default":4.8,"question":"Integrity","id":"integrity","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":4.8,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"availability":{"type":"slider","default":3.5,"question":"Availability","id":"availability","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.5,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"additionalInformation":{"sectionTitle":"Additional Information","sectionId":8,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"vrComment1":{"id":"vrComment-1","type":"text","question":"Are you a state or local election official?","show":true,"userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false}},"vrComment2":{"id":"vrComment-2","type":"text","question":"Who maintains the Voter Registration Database (VRDB) software and security?","tooltip":"For information to determine your voter database configuration, go to: https://www.eac.gov/statewide-voter-registration-systems","show":true,"userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false}},"vrComment3":{"id":"vrComment-3","type":"text","question":"What is the name of the Voter Registration Database (VRDB) vendor and service provider?","show":true,"userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false}},"vrComment4":{"id":"vrComment-4","type":"text","question":"What software is used (operating system, applications, web servers, databases)?","show":true,"userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false}},"vrComment5":{"id":"vrComment-5","type":"text","question":"What interconnections exist between the Voter Registration Database (VRDB) and other systems (e.g. Department of Motor Vehicles)?","show":true,"userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false}}}}},"pollbookPrepQuestions":{"scaleQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Scale of Pollbook Preparation","sectionId":1,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"jurisdictionOrState":{"question":"Is the preparation done at the Jurisdiction or State level?","options":["Jurisdiction","State"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"jurisdictionOrState","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"scale":{"question":"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.","options":["High","Medium","Low"],"type":"dropdown","show":false,"id":"scale","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"tooltip":"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},"accessQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Access to Pollbook Preparation System","sectionId":2,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"remoteAccess":{"question":"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"remoteAccess","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"question":"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"remoteAccessNoAuth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"anyIPS":{"question":"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"anyIPS","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System","service":"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B","tooltip":"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"allowList":{"question":"Do you add IPs to the \'Allow List\'?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"allowList","mitigation":"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses","service":"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy","source":"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf","tooltip":"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"proximateAccess":{"question":"Is there proximate access to the system?","tooltip":"Proximate access refers to \'Bluetooth\' and \'Wifi\'.","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"proximateAccess","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"bluetooth":{"question":"Is Bluetooth enabled?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"bluetooth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wifi":{"question":"Is there WiFi access?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wifi","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wepOrWpa1":{"question":"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wepOrWpa1","mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wpa2":{"question":"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","showMitigation":false,"show":false,"id":"wpa2","mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"physicalMedia":{"question":"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"physicalMedia","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"question":"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","showMitigation":false,"show":false,"id":"removableMediaPolicy","mitigation":"Enact removable media policy","service":"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf","tooltip":"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"authQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Authentication","sectionId":3,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"anyAuth":{"question":"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"showMitigation":false,"id":"anyAuth","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"sfa":{"question":"Do you use single factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"sfa","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"mfa":{"question":"Do you use multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"mfa"},"tfa":{"question":"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","showMitigation":false,"show":false,"id":"tfa","mitigation":"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet","source":"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf","tooltip":"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"ofa":{"question":"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"ofa","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Hardware Management","sectionId":4,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.","questions":{"patchHardware":{"question":"Do you patch the system used for pollbook preparation?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","showMitigation":false,"show":true,"id":"patchHardware","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"patchHardwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the system prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"patchHardwareElection","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Software Management","sectionId":5,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.","questions":{"patchSoftware":{"question":"Do you patch your application software used to prepare pollbooks?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","showMitigation":false,"show":true,"id":"patchSoftware","mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the software prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"patchSoftwareElection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"DDoS Protection","sectionId":6,"complete":false,"tooltip":"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.","questions":{"ddosProtection":{"question":"Do you have DDoS protection for your server?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","showMitigation":false,"show":true,"id":"ddosProtection","mitigation":"Implement DDoS protection","service":"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Importance Values","color":"white","sectionId":7,"complete":true,"comments":null,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"confidentiality":{"type":"slider","default":2.7,"question":"Confidentiality","id":"confidentiality","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":2.7,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"integrity":{"type":"slider","default":3.8,"question":"Integrity","id":"integrity","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.8,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"availability":{"type":"slider","default":3.1,"question":"Availability","id":"availability","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.1,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"additionalInformation":{"sectionTitle":"Additional Information","color":"white","sectionId":8,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"pbComment1":{"id":"pbComment-1","type":"text","question":"Who is the pollbook prepared by?","show":true,"userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false}},"pbComment2":{"id":"pbComment-2","type":"text","question":"Who manages pollbook preparation? (Local Jurisdiction, State, or vendor)","show":true,"userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false}},"pbComment3":{"id":"pbComment-3","type":"text","question":"What is the name, make, and model of the System used to prepare the pollbook?","show":true,"userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false}}}}},"pollbookUseQuestions":{"scaleQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Scale of Pollbook Use","sectionId":1,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"networkedOrNonNetworked":{"question":"Is the pollbook networked or non-networked?","options":["Networked","Non-Networked"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"networkedOrNonNetworked"},"jurisdictionOrState":{"question":"Is the pollbook used at the Jurisdiction or State level?","options":["Jurisdiction","State"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"jurisdictionOrState"},"scale":{"question":"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.","options":["High","Medium","Low"],"type":"dropdown","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"scale","tooltip":"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},"accessQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Access to Pollbook","sectionId":2,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"remoteAccess":{"question":"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"remoteAccess"},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"question":"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"remoteAccessNoAuth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"anyIPS":{"question":"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"anyIPS","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System","service":"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B","tooltip":"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity."},"allowList":{"question":"Do you add IPs to the \'Allow List\'?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"allowList","mitigation":"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses","service":"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy","source":"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf","tooltip":"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses."},"proximateAccess":{"question":"Is there proximate access to the system?","tooltip":"Proximate access refers to \'Bluetooth\' and \'Wifi\'.","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"proximateAccess"},"bluetooth":{"question":"Is Bluetooth enabled?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"bluetooth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":null},"wifi":{"question":"Is there WiFi access?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wifi","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"tooltip":null},"wepOrWpa1":{"question":"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wepOrWpa1","mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks."},"wpa2":{"question":"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"showMitigation":false,"show":false,"id":"wpa2","mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP."},"physicalMedia":{"question":"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"physicalMedia"},"removableMediaPolicy":{"question":"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"showMitigation":false,"show":false,"id":"removableMediaPolicy","mitigation":"Enact removable media policy","service":"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf","tooltip":"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question."}}},"authQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Authentication","sectionId":3,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"anyAuth":{"question":"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"showMitigation":false,"id":"anyAuth","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},"sfa":{"question":"Do you use single factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"sfa","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},"mfa":{"question":"Do you use multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"mfa"},"tfa":{"question":"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"showMitigation":false,"show":false,"id":"tfa","mitigation":"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet","source":"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf","tooltip":"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”."},"ofa":{"question":"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"ofa","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator"}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Hardware Management","sectionId":4,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.","questions":{"patchHardware":{"question":"Do you keep the pollbook system updated and patched?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"showMitigation":false,"show":true,"id":"patchHardware","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null},"patchHardwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the system prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"patchHardwareElection","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null}}},"softwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Software Management","sectionId":5,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.","questions":{"patchSoftware":{"question":"Do you patch your pollbook application software?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"showMitigation":false,"show":true,"id":"patchSoftware","mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/"},"patchSoftwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the software prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"patchSoftwareElection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null}}},"ddosQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"DDoS Protection","sectionId":6,"complete":false,"tooltip":"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.","questions":{"ddosProtection":{"question":"Do you have DDoS protection for your server?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"showMitigation":false,"show":true,"id":"ddosProtection","mitigation":"Implement DDoS protection","service":"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf"}}},"importanceQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Importance Values","sectionId":7,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"confidentiality":{"type":"slider","default":2.7,"question":"Confidentiality","id":"confidentiality","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":2.7,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"integrity":{"type":"slider","default":3.8,"question":"Integrity","id":"integrity","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.8,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"availability":{"type":"slider","default":3.1,"question":"Availability","id":"availability","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.1,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}}},"ballotPrepQuestions":{"scaleQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Scale of Ballot Preparation","sectionId":1,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"jurisdictionOrState":{"question":"Is the preparation done at the Jurisdiction or State level?","options":["Jurisdiction","State"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"jurisdictionOrState","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"scale":{"question":"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.","tooltip":"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>","options":["High","Medium","Low"],"type":"dropdown","show":false,"id":"scale","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"accessQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Access to the Ballot Preparation System","sectionId":2,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"remoteAccess":{"question":"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"remoteAccess","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"question":"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"remoteAccessNoAuth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"anyIPS":{"question":"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"anyIPS","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System","service":"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B","tooltip":"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"allowList":{"question":"Do you add IPs to the \'Allow List\'?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"allowList","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses","service":"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy","source":"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf","tooltip":"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"ballotLoading":{"question":"Do you transmit ballot definition files using an external network (e.g. VPN, internet, or web portal)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"ballotLoading","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"service":null,"source":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"proximateAccess":{"question":"Is there proximate access to the system?","tooltip":"Proximate access refers to \'Bluetooth\' and \'Wifi\'.","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"proximateAccess","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"bluetooth":{"question":"Is Bluetooth enabled?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"bluetooth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wifi":{"question":"Is there WiFi access?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wifi","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wepOrWpa1":{"question":"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wepOrWpa1","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wpa2":{"question":"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wpa2","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"physicalMedia":{"question":"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"physicalMedia","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"question":"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"removableMediaPolicy","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Enact removable media policy","service":"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf","tooltip":"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"authQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Authentication","sectionId":3,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"anyAuth":{"question":"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"anyAuth","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"sfa":{"question":"Do you use single factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"sfa","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"mfa":{"question":"Do you use multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"mfa","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"tfa":{"question":"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"tfa","mitigation":"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet","source":"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf","tooltip":"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"ofa":{"question":"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"ofa","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Hardware Management","sectionId":4,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.","questions":{"patchHardware":{"question":"Do you patch the system used to prepare the ballot?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"patchHardware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":"Ballot preparation systems may include ballot layout and generation software.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"patchHardwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the system prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"patchHardwareElection","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Software Management","sectionId":5,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.","questions":{"patchSoftware":{"question":"Do you patch your ballot preparation software?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"patchSoftware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the software prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"patchSoftwareElection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"DDoS Protection","sectionId":6,"complete":false,"tooltip":"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.","questions":{"ddosProtection":{"question":"Do you have DDoS protection for the system used for ballot preparation?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"ddosProtection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Implement DDoS protection","service":"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Importance Values","sectionId":7,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"confidentiality":{"type":"slider","default":2.9,"question":"Confidentiality","id":"confidentiality","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":2.9,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"integrity":{"type":"slider","default":4.9,"question":"Integrity","id":"integrity","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":4.9,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"availability":{"type":"slider","default":3.6,"question":"Availability","id":"availability","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.6,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"additionalInformation":{"sectionTitle":"Additional Information","sectionId":8,"complete":true,"questions":{"bpComment1":{"id":"bpComment-1","type":"text","question":"Who manages ballot preparation? (Local Jurisdiction, State, or vendor)","show":true,"userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false}},"bpComment2":{"id":"bpComment-2","type":"text","question":"What is the name, make, and model of the System used to prepare ballots?","show":true,"userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false}}}}},"votingMachinePrepQuestions":{"scaleQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Scale of Voting Machine Preparation","sectionId":1,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"jurisdictionOrState":{"question":"Is the preparation done at the Jurisdiction or State level?","options":["Jurisdiction","State"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"jurisdictionOrState"},"scale":{"question":"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.","options":["High","Medium","Low"],"type":"dropdown","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"scale","tooltip":"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},"accessQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Access to Voting Machine Preparation System","sectionId":2,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"remoteAccess":{"question":"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"remoteAccess"},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"question":"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"remoteAccessNoAuth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"anyIPS":{"question":"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"anyIPS","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System","service":"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B","tooltip":"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity."},"allowList":{"question":"Do you add IPs to the \'Allow List\'?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"allowList","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses","service":"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy","source":"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf","tooltip":"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses."},"machineProgramming":{"question":"Is the voting machine programmed through an external network? (e.g. Virtual Private Network (VPN), Internet, etc)","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"machineProgramming","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"service":null,"source":null},"proximateAccess":{"question":"Is there proximate access to the system?","tooltip":"Proximate access refers to \'Bluetooth\' and \'Wifi\'.","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"proximateAccess"},"bluetooth":{"question":"Is Bluetooth enabled?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"bluetooth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":null},"wifi":{"question":"Is there WiFi access?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wifi","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"tooltip":null},"wepOrWpa1":{"question":"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wepOrWpa1","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks."},"wpa2":{"question":"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wpa2","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP."},"physicalMedia":{"question":"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"physicalMedia"},"removableMediaPolicy":{"question":"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"removableMediaPolicy","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Enact removable media policy","service":"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf","tooltip":"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question."}}},"authQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Authentication","sectionId":3,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"anyAuth":{"question":"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"anyAuth","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},"sfa":{"question":"Do you use single factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"sfa","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},"mfa":{"question":"Do you use multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"mfa"},"tfa":{"question":"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"tfa","mitigation":"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet","source":"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf","tooltip":"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”."},"ofa":{"question":"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"ofa","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator"}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Hardware Management","sectionId":4,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.","questions":{"patchHardware":{"question":"Do you patch the server or system used to prepare voting machines?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"patchHardware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null},"patchHardwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the server or system prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"patchHardwareElection","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null}}},"softwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Software Management","sectionId":5,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.","questions":{"patchSoftware":{"question":"Do you patch your application software used to prepare voting machines?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"patchSoftware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/"},"patchSoftwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the software prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"patchSoftwareElection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null}}},"ddosQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"DDoS Protection","sectionId":6,"complete":false,"tooltip":"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.","questions":{"ddosProtection":{"question":"Do you have DDoS when programming a ballot on a voting machine?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"ddosProtection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation","service":"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf"}}},"importanceQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Importance Values","sectionId":7,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"confidentiality":{"type":"slider","default":2.9,"question":"Confidentiality","id":"confidentiality","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":2.9,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"integrity":{"type":"slider","default":4.9,"question":"Integrity","id":"integrity","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":4.9,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"availability":{"type":"slider","default":3.6,"question":"Availability","id":"availability","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.6,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"additionalInformation":{"sectionTitle":"Additional Information","sectionId":8,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"vmpComment1":{"id":"vmpComment-1","type":"text","question":"What System is used for voting machine preparation? (State or Local System) ","userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true},"vmpComment2":{"id":"vmpComment-2","type":"text","question":"What is the name, make, and model of the System used for voting machine preparation?","userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true}}}},"votingMachineUseQuestions":{"scaleQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Scale of Voting Machine Use","sectionId":1,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"networkedOrNonNetworked":{"question":"Is the voting machine networked or non-networked during voting?","options":["Networked","Non-Networked"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"networkedOrNonNetworked"},"jurisdictionOrState":{"question":"Is the machine managed at the Jurisdiction or State level?","options":["Jurisdiction","State"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"jurisdictionOrState"},"scale":{"question":"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.","options":["High","Medium","Low"],"type":"dropdown","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"scale","tooltip":"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},"accessQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Access to Voting Machines During Use","sectionId":2,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"remoteAccess":{"question":"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"remoteAccess"},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"question":"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"remoteAccessNoAuth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"anyIPS":{"question":"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"anyIPS","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System","service":"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B","tooltip":"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity."},"allowList":{"question":"Do you add IPs to the \'Allow List\'?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"allowList","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses","service":"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy","source":"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf","tooltip":"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses."},"proximateAccess":{"question":"Is there proximate access to the system?","tooltip":"Proximate access refers to \'Bluetooth\' and \'Wifi\'.","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"proximateAccess"},"bluetooth":{"question":"Is Bluetooth enabled?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"bluetooth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":null},"wifi":{"question":"Is there WiFi access?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wifi","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"tooltip":null},"wepOrWpa1":{"question":"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wepOrWpa1","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks."},"wpa2":{"question":"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wpa2","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP."},"physicalMedia":{"question":"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"physicalMedia"},"removableMediaPolicy":{"question":"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"removableMediaPolicy","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Enact removable media policy","service":"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf","tooltip":"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question."}}},"authQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Authentication","sectionId":3,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"anyAuth":{"question":"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"anyAuth","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},"sfa":{"question":"Do you use single factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"sfa","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},"mfa":{"question":"Do you use multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"mfa"},"tfa":{"question":"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"tfa","mitigation":"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet","source":"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf","tooltip":"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”."},"ofa":{"question":"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"ofa","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator"}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Hardware Management","sectionId":4,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.","questions":{"patchHardware":{"question":"Do you patch the voting machines?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"patchHardware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null},"patchHardwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the machines prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"patchHardwareElection","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null}}},"softwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Software Management","sectionId":5,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.","questions":{"patchSoftware":{"question":"Do you patch any specialized application software used on the voting machines?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"patchSoftware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/"},"patchSoftwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the software prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"patchSoftwareElection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null}}},"ddosQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"DDoS Protection","sectionId":6,"complete":false,"tooltip":"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.","questions":{"ddosProtection":{"question":"Do you have DDoS protection when uploading ballot files to a voting machine?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"ddosProtection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation","service":"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf"}}},"importanceQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Importance Values","sectionId":7,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"confidentiality":{"type":"slider","default":2.9,"question":"Confidentiality","id":"confidentiality","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":2.9,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"integrity":{"type":"slider","default":4.9,"question":"Integrity","id":"integrity","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":4.9,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"availability":{"type":"slider","default":3.6,"question":"Availability","id":"availability","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.6,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"additionalInformation":{"sectionTitle":"Additional Information","sectionId":8,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"vmuComment1":{"id":"vmuComment-1","type":"text","question":"What is the make and model of the voting machines?","userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true},"vmuComment2":{"id":"vmuComment-2","type":"text","question":"Do the voting machines maintain a voter verified paper record?","userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true}}}},"tabulationPrepQuestions":{"scaleQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Scale of Tabulation Preparation","sectionId":1,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"scale":{"question":"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.","options":["High","Medium","Low"],"type":"dropdown","userInput":{"answer":"Medium","comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"scale","tooltip":"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},"accessQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Access to Tabulation Preparation System","sectionId":2,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"remoteAccess":{"question":"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"remoteAccess"},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"question":"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"remoteAccessNoAuth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"anyIPS":{"question":"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"anyIPS","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System","service":"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B","tooltip":"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity."},"allowList":{"question":"Do you add IPs to the \'Allow List\'?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"allowList","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses","service":"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy","source":"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf","tooltip":"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses."},"proximateAccess":{"question":"Is there proximate access to the system?","tooltip":"Proximate access refers to \'Bluetooth\' and \'Wifi\'.","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"proximateAccess"},"bluetooth":{"question":"Is Bluetooth enabled?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"bluetooth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":null},"wifi":{"question":"Is there WiFi access?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wifi","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"tooltip":null},"wepOrWpa1":{"question":"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wepOrWpa1","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks."},"wpa2":{"question":"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wpa2","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP."},"physicalMedia":{"question":"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"physicalMedia"},"removableMediaPolicy":{"question":"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"removableMediaPolicy","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Enact removable media policy","service":"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf","tooltip":"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question."}}},"authQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Authentication","sectionId":3,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"anyAuth":{"question":"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"anyAuth","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},"sfa":{"question":"Do you use single factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"sfa","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},"mfa":{"question":"Do you use multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"mfa"},"tfa":{"question":"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"tfa","mitigation":"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet","source":"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf","tooltip":"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”."},"ofa":{"question":"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"ofa","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator"}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Hardware Management","sectionId":4,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.","questions":{"patchHardware":{"question":"Do you patch the server or system used to prepare tabulation devices?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"patchHardware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null},"patchHardwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the server or system prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"patchHardwareElection","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null}}},"softwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Software Management","sectionId":5,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.","questions":{"patchSoftware":{"question":"Do you patch your application software for tabulation preparation?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"patchSoftware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/"},"patchSoftwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the software prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"patchSoftwareElection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null}}},"ddosQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"DDoS Protection","sectionId":6,"complete":false,"tooltip":"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.","questions":{"ddosProtection":{"question":"If you network or modem results, do you have DDoS protection on your backend server?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"ddosProtection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation","service":"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf"},"machineProgramming":{"question":"Do you prepare tabulation equipment using an external network? (e.g. Virtual Private Network (VPN), internet, offsite warehouse connection)","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"machineProgramming","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"service":null,"source":null}}},"importanceQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Importance Values","sectionId":7,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"confidentiality":{"type":"slider","default":2.2,"question":"Confidentiality","id":"confidentiality","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":2.2,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"integrity":{"type":"slider","default":4.9,"question":"Integrity","id":"integrity","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":4.9,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"availability":{"type":"slider","default":3.1,"question":"Availability","id":"availability","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.1,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"additionalInformation":{"sectionTitle":"Additional Information","sectionId":8,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"tabPrepComment1":{"id":"tabPrepComment-1","type":"text","question":"What System is used for tabulation preparation? (State or Local System)","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true},"tabPrepComment2":{"id":"tabPrepComment-2","type":"text","question":"What is the name, make, and model of the System used for tabulation preparation?","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true}}}},"precinctTabulationQuestions":{"scaleQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Scale of Precinct Tabulation","sectionId":1,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"tabulationAtPrecincts":{"question":"Do you use precinct scanners or DREs that tabulate in the precincts?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"tabulationAtPrecincts","tooltip":"DRE: Direct-Recording Electronic voting machines"},"networkedOrNonNetworked":{"question":"Is the precinct tabulator networked (e.g., modeming) or non-networked?","options":["Networked","Non-Networked"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"networkedOrNonNetworked"},"scale":{"question":"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.","options":["High","Medium","Low","N/A"],"type":"dropdown","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"scale","tooltip":"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},"accessQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Access to Precinct Tabulation System","sectionId":2,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"remoteAccess":{"question":"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"remoteAccess"},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"question":"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"remoteAccessNoAuth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"anyIPS":{"question":"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"anyIPS","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System","service":"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B","tooltip":"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity."},"allowList":{"question":"Do you add IPs to the \'Allow List\'?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"allowList","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses","service":"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy","source":"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf","tooltip":"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses."},"proximateAccess":{"question":"Is there proximate access to the system?","tooltip":"Proximate access refers to \'Bluetooth\' and \'Wifi\'.","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"proximateAccess"},"bluetooth":{"question":"Is Bluetooth enabled?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"bluetooth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":null},"wifi":{"question":"Is there WiFi access?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wifi","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"tooltip":null},"wepOrWpa1":{"question":"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wepOrWpa1","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks."},"wpa2":{"question":"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wpa2","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP."},"physicalMedia":{"question":"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"physicalMedia"},"removableMediaPolicy":{"question":"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"removableMediaPolicy","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Enact removable media policy","service":"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf","tooltip":"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question."}}},"authQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Authentication","sectionId":3,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"anyAuth":{"question":"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"anyAuth","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},"sfa":{"question":"Do you use single factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"sfa","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},"mfa":{"question":"Do you use multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"mfa"},"tfa":{"question":"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"tfa","mitigation":"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet","source":"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf","tooltip":"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”."},"ofa":{"question":"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"ofa","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator"}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Hardware Management","sectionId":4,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.","questions":{"patchHardware":{"question":"Do you patch the system used for precinct tabulation?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"patchHardware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null},"patchHardwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the system prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"patchHardwareElection","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null}}},"softwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Software Management","sectionId":5,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.","questions":{"patchSoftware":{"question":"Do you patch any specialized application software used for precinct tabulation?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"patchSoftware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/"},"patchSoftwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the software prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"patchSoftwareElection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null}}},"ddosQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"DDoS Protection","sectionId":6,"complete":false,"tooltip":"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.","questions":{"ddosProtection":{"question":"If you network or modem results, do you have DDoS protection on your backend server?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"ddosProtection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation","service":"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf"}}},"importanceQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Importance Values","sectionId":7,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"confidentiality":{"type":"slider","default":2.2,"question":"Confidentiality","id":"confidentiality","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":2.2,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"integrity":{"type":"slider","default":4.9,"question":"Integrity","id":"integrity","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":4.9,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"availability":{"type":"slider","default":3.1,"question":"Availability","id":"availability","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.1,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"additionalInformation":{"sectionTitle":"Additional Information","sectionId":8,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"precinctTabComment1":{"id":"precinctTabComment-1","type":"text","question":"What is the make and model of the tabulation machines?","userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true}}}},"centralTabulationQuestions":{"scaleQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Scale of Central Tabulation","sectionId":1,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"networkedOrNonNetworked":{"question":"Is the central tabulation system networked or non-networked?","options":["Networked","Non-Networked"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"networkedOrNonNetworked"},"jurisdictionOrState":{"question":"Is tabulation occurring centrally at the jurisdiction or state level?","options":["Jurisdiction","State"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"jurisdictionOrState","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"scale":{"question":"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.","options":["High","Medium","Low"],"type":"dropdown","show":false,"id":"scale","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"tooltip":"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},"accessQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Access to Central Tabulation System and Devices","sectionId":2,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"remoteAccess":{"question":"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"remoteAccess","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"question":"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"remoteAccessNoAuth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"anyIPS":{"question":"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"anyIPS","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System","service":"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B","tooltip":"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"allowList":{"question":"Do you add IPs to the \'Allow List\'?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"allowList","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses","service":"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy","source":"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf","tooltip":"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"proximateAccess":{"question":"Is there proximate access to the system?","tooltip":"Proximate access refers to \'Bluetooth\' and \'Wifi\'.","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"proximateAccess","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"bluetooth":{"question":"Is Bluetooth enabled?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"bluetooth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wifi":{"question":"Is there WiFi access?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wifi","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wepOrWpa1":{"question":"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wepOrWpa1","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wpa2":{"question":"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wpa2","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"physicalMedia":{"question":"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"physicalMedia","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"question":"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"removableMediaPolicy","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Enact removable media policy","service":"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf","tooltip":"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"authQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Authentication","sectionId":3,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"anyAuth":{"question":"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"anyAuth","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"sfa":{"question":"Do you use single factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"sfa","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"mfa":{"question":"Do you use multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"mfa","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"tfa":{"question":"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"tfa","mitigation":"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet","source":"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf","tooltip":"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"ofa":{"question":"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"ofa","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Hardware Management","sectionId":4,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.","questions":{"patchHardware":{"question":"Do you patch the system used for central tabulation?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"patchHardware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"patchHardwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the system prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"patchHardwareElection","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Software Management","sectionId":5,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.","questions":{"patchSoftware":{"question":"Do you patch any specialized application software used for central tabulation?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"patchSoftware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the software prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"patchSoftwareElection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"DDoS Protection","sectionId":6,"complete":false,"tooltip":"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.","questions":{"ddosProtection":{"question":"If you network or modem results, do you have DDoS protection on your backend server?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"ddosProtection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation","service":"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Importance Values","sectionId":7,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"confidentiality":{"type":"slider","default":2.2,"question":"Confidentiality","id":"confidentiality","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":2.2,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"integrity":{"type":"slider","default":4.9,"question":"Integrity","id":"integrity","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":4.9,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"availability":{"type":"slider","default":3.1,"question":"Availability","id":"availability","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.1,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"additionalInformation":{"sectionTitle":"Additional Information","sectionId":8,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"ctComment1":{"id":"ctComment-1","type":"text","question":"What is the make and model of the tabulation machines?","show":true,"userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false}},"ctComment2":{"id":"ctComment-2","type":"text","question":"What type of output on vote count do the tabulation machines produce?","show":true,"userInput":{"answer":null,"bookmarked":false}}}}},"aggregationQuestions":{"scaleQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Scale of State Level Aggregation","sectionId":1,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"scale":{"question":"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.","options":["High","Medium","Low"],"type":"dropdown","show":true,"id":"scale","userInput":{"answer":"High","comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"tooltip":"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},"accessQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Access to State Level Aggregation System","sectionId":2,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"remoteAccess":{"question":"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"remoteAccess","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"question":"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"remoteAccessNoAuth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"anyIPS":{"question":"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"anyIPS","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System","service":"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B","tooltip":"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"allowList":{"question":"Do you add IPs to the \'Allow List\'?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"allowList","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses","service":"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy","source":"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf","tooltip":"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"proximateAccess":{"question":"Is there proximate access to the system?","tooltip":"Proximate access refers to \'Bluetooth\' and \'Wifi\'.","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"proximateAccess","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"bluetooth":{"question":"Is Bluetooth enabled?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"bluetooth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wifi":{"question":"Is there WiFi access?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wifi","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wepOrWpa1":{"question":"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wepOrWpa1","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"wpa2":{"question":"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"wpa2","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"physicalMedia":{"question":"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"physicalMedia","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"question":"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"removableMediaPolicy","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Enact removable media policy","service":"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf","tooltip":"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"authQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Authentication","sectionId":3,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"anyAuth":{"question":"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"anyAuth","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"sfa":{"question":"Do you use single factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"sfa","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"mfa":{"question":"Do you use multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"mfa","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"tfa":{"question":"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"tfa","mitigation":"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet","source":"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf","tooltip":"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"ofa":{"question":"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"ofa","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Hardware Management","sectionId":4,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.","questions":{"patchHardware":{"question":"Do you patch the server used to aggregate votes at the State level?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","answer":null,"show":true,"id":"patchHardware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"patchHardwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the server prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"patchHardwareElection","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Software Management","sectionId":5,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.","questions":{"patchSoftware":{"question":"Do you patch any specialized application software used for State level vote aggregation?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"patchSoftware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"question":"Is it patched prior to each election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"patchSoftwareElection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null,"userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"DDoS Protection","sectionId":6,"complete":false,"tooltip":"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.","questions":{"ddosProtection":{"question":"Do you have DDoS protection for your server?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":true,"id":"ddosProtection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation","service":"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Importance Values","color":"white","sectionId":7,"complete":true,"comments":null,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"confidentiality":{"type":"slider","default":2.2,"question":"Confidentiality","id":"confidentiality","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":2.2,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"integrity":{"type":"slider","default":4.9,"question":"Integrity","id":"integrity","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":4.9,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"availability":{"type":"slider","default":3.1,"question":"Availability","id":"availability","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":3.1,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}}},"websiteQuestions":{"scaleQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Scale of Website","sectionId":1,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"scale":{"question":"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.","options":["High","Medium","Low"],"type":"dropdown","userInput":{"answer":"High","comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"scale","tooltip":"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},"accessQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Access to Website Management System","sectionId":2,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"remoteAccess":{"question":"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"remoteAccess"},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"question":"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","show":false,"id":"remoteAccessNoAuth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"anyIPS":{"question":"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"anyIPS","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System","service":"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B","tooltip":"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity."},"allowList":{"question":"Do you add IPs to the \'Allow List\'?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"allowList","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses","service":"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy","source":"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf","tooltip":"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses."},"proximateAccess":{"question":"Is there proximate access to the system?","tooltip":"Proximate access refers to \'Bluetooth\' and \'Wifi\'.","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"proximateAccess"},"bluetooth":{"question":"Is Bluetooth enabled?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"bluetooth","mitigation":null,"tooltip":null},"wifi":{"question":"Is there WiFi access?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wifi","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":null,"tooltip":null},"wepOrWpa1":{"question":"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wepOrWpa1","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks."},"wpa2":{"question":"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"wpa2","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use better encryption (WPA2)","service":"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf","tooltip":"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP."},"physicalMedia":{"question":"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"physicalMedia"},"removableMediaPolicy":{"question":"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"removableMediaPolicy","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Enact removable media policy","service":"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf","tooltip":"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question."}}},"authQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Authentication","sectionId":3,"complete":false,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"anyAuth":{"question":"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"anyAuth","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},"sfa":{"question":"Do you use single factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"sfa","mitigation":"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},"mfa":{"question":"Do you use multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"mfa"},"tfa":{"question":"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"tfa","mitigation":"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)","service":"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet","source":"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf","tooltip":"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”."},"ofa":{"question":"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"ofa","mitigation":null,"tooltip":"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator"}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Hardware Management","sectionId":4,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.","questions":{"patchHardware":{"question":"Do you patch the server used to host your website?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"patchHardware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null},"patchHardwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the server more frequently than once per election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"showMitigation":false,"id":"patchHardwareElection","mitigation":"Patch server regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null}}},"softwareQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Software Management","sectionId":5,"complete":false,"tooltip":"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.","questions":{"patchSoftware":{"question":"Do you patch any specialized application software used to manage your website?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"patchSoftware","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/"},"patchSoftwareElection":{"question":"Do you patch the software more frequently than once per election?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":false,"id":"patchSoftwareElection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Patch software regularly","service":"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems","source":"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/","tooltip":null}}},"ddosQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"DDoS Protection","sectionId":6,"complete":false,"tooltip":"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.","questions":{"ddosProtection":{"question":"Do you have DDoS protection for your server?","options":["Yes","No"],"type":"radio","userInput":{"answer":null,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false},"show":true,"id":"ddosProtection","showMitigation":false,"mitigation":"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation","service":"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide","source":"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf"}}},"importanceQuestions":{"sectionTitle":"Importance Values","sectionId":7,"complete":true,"tooltip":null,"questions":{"confidentiality":{"type":"slider","default":1.5,"question":"Confidentiality","id":"confidentiality","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":1.5,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"integrity":{"type":"slider","default":4.3,"question":"Integrity","id":"integrity","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":4.3,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}},"availability":{"type":"slider","default":2.1,"question":"Availability","id":"availability","show":true,"userInput":{"userValue":2.1,"comments":null,"bookmarked":false}}}}},"voterRegistrationVisited":false,"pollbookPrepVisited":false,"pollbookUseVisited":false,"ballotPrepVisited":false,"votingMachinePrepVisited":false,"votingMachineUseVisited":false,"tabulationPrepVisited":false,"precinctTabulationVisited":false,"centralTabulationVisited":false,"aggregationVisited":false,"websiteVisited":false}')},"53d7":function(e,t,o){"use strict";var i=o("1a7b"),s=o.n(i);s.a},"5c0b":function(e,t,o){"use strict";var i=o("7694"),s=o.n(i);s.a},7694:function(e,t,o){},"7e11":function(e,t,o){"use strict";var i=o("d681"),s=o.n(i);s.a},"93ad":function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('{"$id":"electionSurveySchema","type":"object","properties":{"voterRegistrationQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scaleQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Scale of Voter Registration Database (VRDB)"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[1]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"jurisdictionOrState":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"valid":{"type":"string","enum":["Jurisdiction","State"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["jurisdictionOrState"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Jurisdiction","State",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"scale":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":3,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["High","Medium","Low"]}},"type":{"enum":["dropdown"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["scale"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["High","Medium","Low",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"accessQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Access to Voter Registration Database (VRDB)"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[2]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"remoteAccess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccessNoAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"anyIPS":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyIPS"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"allowList":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["allowList"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"proximateACcess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["proximateAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"bluetooth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["bluetooth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wifi":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wifi"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wepOrWpa1":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wepOrWpa1"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wpa2":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wpa2"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"physicalMedia":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["physicalMedia"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["removableMediaPolicy"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"authQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Authentication"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[3]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"anyAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"sfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["sfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"mfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["mfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"tfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["tfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ofa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ofa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Hardware Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[4]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchHardware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchHardwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Software Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[5]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchSoftware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["DDoS Protection"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[6]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"ddosProtection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ddosProtection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Importance Values"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[7]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"confidentiality":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["confidentiality"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"integrity":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["integrity"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"availability":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["availability"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"additionalQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Additional Information"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[8]},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"vrComment1":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["vr-Comment1"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"vrComment2":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["vr-Comment2"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"vrComment3":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["vr-Comment3"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"vrComment4":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["vr-Comment4"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"vrComment5":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["vr-Comment5"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}}}},"pollbookPrepQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scaleQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Scale of Pollbook Preparation"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[1]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"jurisdictionOrState":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"valid":{"type":"string","enum":["Jurisdiction","State"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["jurisdictionOrState"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Jurisdiction","State",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"scale":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":3,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["High","Medium","Low"]}},"type":{"enum":["dropdown"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["scale"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["High","Medium","Low",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"accessQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Access to Pollbook Preparation System"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[2]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"remoteAccess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccessNoAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"anyIPS":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyIPS"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"allowList":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["allowList"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"proximateAccess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["proximateAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"bluetooth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["bluetooth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wifi":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wifi"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wepOrWpa1":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wepOrWpa1"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wpa2":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wpa2"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"physicalMedia":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["physicalMedia"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["removableMediaPolicy"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"authQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Authentication"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[3]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"anyAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"sfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["sfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"mfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["mfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"tfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["tfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ofa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ofa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Hardware Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[4]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchHardware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchHardwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Software Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[5]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchSoftware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["DDoS Protection"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[6]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"ddosProtection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ddosProtection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Importance Values"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[7]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"confidentiality":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["confidentiality"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"integrity":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["integrity"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"availability":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["availability"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"additionalQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Additional Information"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[8]},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"pbComment1":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["pbComment1"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"pbComment2":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["pbComment2"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"pbComment3":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["pbComment3"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}}}},"pollbookUseQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scaleQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Scale of Pollbook Use"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[1]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"networkedOrNonNetworked":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"valid":{"type":"string","enum":["Networked","Non-Networked"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["networkedOrNonNetworked"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Networked","Non-Networked",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"jurisdictionOrState":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"valid":{"type":"string","enum":["Jurisdiction","State"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["jurisdictionOrState"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Jurisdiction","State",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"scale":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":3,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["High","Medium","Low"]}},"type":{"enum":["dropdown"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["scale"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["High","Medium","Low",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"accessQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Access to Pollbook"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[2]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"remoteAccess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccessNoAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"anyIPS":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyIPS"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"allowList":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["allowList"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"proximateACcess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["proximateAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"bluetooth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["bluetooth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wifi":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wifi"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wepOrWpa1":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wepOrWpa1"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wpa2":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wpa2"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"physicalMedia":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["physicalMedia"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["removableMediaPolicy"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"authQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Authentication"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[3]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"anyAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"sfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["sfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"mfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["mfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"tfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["tfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ofa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ofa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Hardware Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[4]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchHardware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchHardwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Software Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[5]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchSoftware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["DDoS Protection"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[6]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"ddosProtection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ddosProtection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Importance Values"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[7]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"confidentiality":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["confidentiality"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"integrity":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["integrity"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"availability":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["availability"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}}}},"ballotPrepQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scaleQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Scale of Ballot Preparation"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[1]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"jurisdictionOrState":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"valid":{"type":"string","enum":["Jurisdiction","State"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["jurisdictionOrState"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Jurisdiction","State",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"scale":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":3,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["High","Medium","Low"]}},"type":{"enum":["dropdown"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["scale"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["High","Medium","Low",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"accessQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Access to the Ballot Preparation System"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[2]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"remoteAccess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccessNoAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"anyIPS":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyIPS"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"allowList":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["allowList"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ballotLoading":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ballotLoading"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"proximateACcess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["proximateAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"bluetooth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["bluetooth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wifi":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wifi"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wepOrWpa1":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wepOrWpa1"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wpa2":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wpa2"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"physicalMedia":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["physicalMedia"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["removableMediaPolicy"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"authQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Authentication"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[3]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"anyAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"sfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["sfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"mfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["mfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"tfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["tfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ofa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ofa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Hardware Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[4]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchHardware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchHardwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Software Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[5]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchSoftware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["DDoS Protection"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[6]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"ddosProtection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ddosProtection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Importance Values"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[7]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"confidentiality":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["confidentiality"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"integrity":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["integrity"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"availability":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["availability"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"additionalQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Additional Information"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[8]},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"bpComment1":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["bpComment-1"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"bpComment2":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["bpComment-2"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}}}},"votingMachinePrepQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scaleQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Scale of Voting Machine Preparation"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[1]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"jurisdictionOrState":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"valid":{"type":"string","enum":["Jurisdiction","State"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["jurisdictionOrState"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Jurisdiction","State",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"scale":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":3,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["High","Medium","Low"]}},"type":{"enum":["dropdown"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["scale"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["High","Medium","Low",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"accessQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Access to Voting Machine Preparation System"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[2]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"remoteAccess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccessNoAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"anyIPS":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyIPS"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"allowList":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["allowList"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"machineProgramming":{"properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["machineProgramming"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"proximateACcess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["proximateAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"bluetooth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["bluetooth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wifi":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wifi"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wepOrWpa1":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wepOrWpa1"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wpa2":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wpa2"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"physicalMedia":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["physicalMedia"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["removableMediaPolicy"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"authQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Authentication"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[3]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"anyAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"sfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["sfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"mfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["mfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"tfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["tfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ofa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ofa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Hardware Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[4]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchHardware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchHardwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Software Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[5]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchSoftware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["DDoS Protection"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[6]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"ddosProtection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ddosProtection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Importance Values"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[7]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"confidentiality":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["confidentiality"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"integrity":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["integrity"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"availability":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["availability"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"additionalQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Additional Information"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[8]},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"vmpComment1":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["vmpComment-1"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"vmpComment2":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["vmpComment-2"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}}}},"votingMachineUseQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scaleQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Scale of Voting Machine Use"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[1]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"networkedOrNonNetworked":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"valid":{"type":"string","enum":["Networked","Non-Networked"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["networkedOrNonNetworked"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Networked","Non-Networked",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"jurisdictionOrState":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"valid":{"type":"string","enum":["Jurisdiction","State"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["jurisdictionOrState"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Jurisdiction","State",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"scale":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":3,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["High","Medium","Low"]}},"type":{"enum":["dropdown"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["scale"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["High","Medium","Low",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"accessQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Access to Voting Machines During Use"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[2]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"remoteAccess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccessNoAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"anyIPS":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyIPS"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"allowList":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["allowList"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"proximateACcess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["proximateAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"bluetooth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["bluetooth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wifi":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wifi"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wepOrWpa1":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wepOrWpa1"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wpa2":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wpa2"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"physicalMedia":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["physicalMedia"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["removableMediaPolicy"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"authQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Authentication"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[3]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"anyAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"sfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["sfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"mfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["mfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"tfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["tfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ofa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ofa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Hardware Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[4]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchHardware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchHardwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Software Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[5]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchSoftware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["DDoS Protection"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[6]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"ddosProtection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ddosProtection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Importance Values"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[7]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"confidentiality":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["confidentiality"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"integrity":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["integrity"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"availability":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["availability"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"additionalQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Additional Information"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[8]},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"vmuComment1":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["vmuComment-1"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"vmuComment2":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["vmuComment-2"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}}}},"tabulationPrepQuestion":{"type":"object","properties":{"scaleQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Scale of Tabulation Preparation"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[1]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scale":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":3,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["High","Medium","Low"]}},"type":{"enum":["dropdown"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["scale"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["High","Medium","Low",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"accessQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Access to Tabulation Preparation System"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[2]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"remoteAccess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccessNoAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"anyIPS":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyIPS"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"allowList":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["allowList"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"proximateACcess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["proximateAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"bluetooth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["bluetooth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wifi":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wifi"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wepOrWpa1":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wepOrWpa1"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wpa2":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wpa2"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"physicalMedia":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["physicalMedia"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["removableMediaPolicy"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"authQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Authentication"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[3]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"anyAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"sfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["sfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"mfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["mfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"tfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["tfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ofa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ofa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Hardware Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[4]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchHardware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchHardwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Software Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[5]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchSoftware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["DDoS Protection"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[6]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"ddosProtection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ddosProtection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"machineProgramming":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["machineProgramming"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Importance Values"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[7]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"confidentiality":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["confidentiality"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"integrity":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["integrity"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"availability":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["availability"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"additionalQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Additional Information"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[8]},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"tabPrepComment1":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["tabPrepComment-1"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"tabPrepComment2":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["tabPrepComment-2"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}}}},"precinctTabulationQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scaleQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Scale of Precinct Tabulation"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[1]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"tabulationAtPrecincts":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["tabulationAtPrecincts"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"networkedOrNonNetworked":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"valid":{"type":"string","enum":["Networked","Non-Networked"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["networkedOrNonNetworked"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Networked","Non-Networked",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"scale":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":4,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["High","Medium","Low","N/A"]}},"type":{"enum":["dropdown"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["scale"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["High","Medium","Low","N/A",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"accessQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Access to Precinct Tabulation System"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[2]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"remoteAccess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccessNoAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"anyIPS":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyIPS"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"allowList":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["allowList"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"proximateACcess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["proximateAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"bluetooth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["bluetooth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wifi":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wifi"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wepOrWpa1":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wepOrWpa1"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wpa2":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wpa2"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"physicalMedia":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["physicalMedia"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["removableMediaPolicy"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"authQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Authentication"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[3]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"anyAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"sfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["sfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"mfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["mfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"tfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["tfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ofa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ofa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Hardware Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[4]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchHardware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchHardwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Software Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[5]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchSoftware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["DDoS Protection"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[6]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"ddosProtection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ddosProtection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Importance Values"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[7]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"confidentiality":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["confidentiality"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"integrity":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["integrity"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"availability":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["availability"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"additionalQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Additional Information"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[8]},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"precinctTabComment1":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["precinctTabComment-1"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}}}},"centralTabulationQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scaleQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Scale of Central Tabulation"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[1]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"jurisdictionOrState":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"valid":{"type":"string","enum":["Jurisdiction","State"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["jurisdictionOrState"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Jurisdiction","State",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"scale":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":3,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["High","Medium","Low"]}},"type":{"enum":["dropdown"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["scale"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["High","Medium","Low",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"accessQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Access to Central Tabulation System and Devices"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[2]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"remoteAccess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccessNoAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"anyIPS":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyIPS"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"allowList":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["allowList"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"proximateACcess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["proximateAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"bluetooth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["bluetooth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wifi":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wifi"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wepOrWpa1":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wepOrWpa1"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wpa2":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wpa2"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"physicalMedia":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["physicalMedia"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["removableMediaPolicy"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"authQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Authentication"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[3]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"anyAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"sfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["sfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"mfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["mfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"tfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["tfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ofa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ofa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Hardware Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[4]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchHardware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchHardwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Software Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[5]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchSoftware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["DDoS Protection"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[6]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"ddosProtection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ddosProtection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Importance Values"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[7]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"confidentiality":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["confidentiality"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"integrity":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["integrity"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"availability":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["availability"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"additionalQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Additional Information"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[8]},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"ctComment1":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["ctComment-1"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ctTabComment2":{"type":"object","properties":{"id":{"enum":["ctComment-2"]},"type":{"enum":["text"]},"question":{"type":"string"},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"answer":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}}}},"aggregationQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scaleQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Scale of State Level Aggregation"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[1]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scale":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":3,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["High","Medium","Low"]}},"type":{"enum":["dropdown"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["scale"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["High","Medium","Low",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"accessQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Access to State Level Aggregation System"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[2]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"remoteAccess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccessNoAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"anyIPS":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyIPS"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"allowList":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["allowList"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"proximateACcess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["proximateAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"bluetooth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["bluetooth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wifi":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wifi"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wepOrWpa1":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wepOrWpa1"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wpa2":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wpa2"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"physicalMedia":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["physicalMedia"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["removableMediaPolicy"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"authQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Authentication"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[3]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"anyAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"sfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["sfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"mfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["mfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"tfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["tfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ofa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ofa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Hardware Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[4]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchHardware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchHardwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Software Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[5]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchSoftware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["DDoS Protection"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[6]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"ddosProtection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ddosProtection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Importance Values"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[7]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"confidentiality":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["confidentiality"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"integrity":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["integrity"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"availability":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["availability"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}}}},"websiteQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scaleQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Scale of Website"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[1]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"scale":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":3,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["High","Medium","Low"]}},"type":{"enum":["dropdown"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["scale"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["High","Medium","Low",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"accessQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Access to Website Management System"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[2]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"remoteAccess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"remoteAccessNoAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["remoteAccessNoAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"anyIPS":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyIPS"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"allowList":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["allowList"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":"string"},"service":{"type":"string"},"source":{"type":"string"},"tooltip":{"type":"string"},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"proximateACcess":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["proximateAccess"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"bluetooth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["bluetooth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wifi":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wifi"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wepOrWpa1":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wepOrWpa1"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"wpa2":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["wpa2"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"physicalMedia":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["physicalMedia"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"removableMediaPolicy":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["removableMediaPolicy"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"authQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Authentication"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[3]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"anyAuth":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["anyAuth"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"sfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["sfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"mfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["mfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"tfa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["tfa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"ofa":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ofa"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"hardwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Hardware Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[4]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchHardware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchHardwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchHardwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"softwareQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Software Management"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[5]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"patchSoftware":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftware"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"patchSoftwareElection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["patchSoftwareElection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"ddosQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["DDoS Protection"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[6]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"ddosProtection":{"type":"object","properties":{"question":{"type":"string"},"options":{"type":"array","maxItems":2,"items":{"type":"string","enum":["Yes","No"]}},"type":{"enum":["radio"]},"show":{"type":"boolean"},"id":{"enum":["ddosProtection"]},"showMitigation":{"type":"boolean"},"mitigation":{"type":["string","null"]},"service":{"type":["string","null"]},"source":{"type":["string","null"]},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"answer":{"enum":["Yes","No",null]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}},"importanceQuestions":{"type":"object","properties":{"sectionTitle":{"enum":["Importance Values"]},"sectionId":{"enum":[7]},"complete":{"type":"boolean"},"tooltip":{"type":["string","null"]},"questions":{"type":"object","properties":{"confidentiality":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["confidentiality"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"integrity":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["integrity"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}},"availability":{"type":"object","properties":{"type":{"enum":["slider"]},"default":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"question":{"type":"string"},"id":{"enum":["availability"]},"show":{"enum":[true]},"userInput":{"type":"object","properties":{"userValue":{"type":"number","maximum":5,"minimum":1},"comments":{"type":["string","null"]},"bookmarked":{"type":"boolean"}}}}}}}}}}},"voterRegistrationVisited":{"type":"boolean"},"pollbookPrepVisited":{"type":"boolean"},"pollbookUseVisited":{"type":"boolean"},"ballotPrepVisited":{"type":"boolean"},"votingMachinePrepVisited":{"type":"boolean"},"votingMachineUseVisited":{"type":"boolean"},"tabulationPrepVisited":{"type":"boolean"},"precinctTabulationVisited":{"type":"boolean"},"centralTabulationVisited":{"type":"boolean"},"aggregationVisited":{"type":"boolean"},"websiteVisited":{"type":"boolean"}}}')},"9b19":function(e,t,o){e.exports=o.p+"img/logo.ad70b7ac.svg"},ad4b:function(e,t,o){e.exports=o.p+"img/upload-answers.f160570a.svg"},b339:function(e,t,o){},b3c5:function(e,t,o){e.exports=o.p+"img/info-icon.67fa1369.svg"},cd49:function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.r(t);o("e260"),o("e6cf"),o("cca6"),o("a79d"),o("db4d");var i=o("2b0e"),s=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("v-app",{attrs:{id:"app"}},[e.isMobile()?e._e():o("Navbar",{staticClass:"no-print"}),e.isMobile()?e._e():o("v-content",[o("router-view")],1),"/"!==e.$route.path||e.isMobile()?e._e():o("Footer",{staticClass:"no-print"}),e.isMobile()?o("MobileWarning"):e._e()],1)},n=[],r=(o("d3b7"),o("4ae1"),o("ac1f"),o("25f0"),o("466d"),o("d4ec")),a=o("bee2"),l=o("262e"),u=o("99de"),p=o("7e84"),c=o("9ab4"),m=o("60a3"),y=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,i=e._self._c||t;return i("v-app-bar",{staticClass:"px-0",attrs:{id:"navbar",app:"",color:"primary",dark:""}},[i("router-link",{staticClass:"d-flex align-center ml-5",attrs:{to:"/"}},[i("v-img",{staticClass:"shrink mr-2",attrs:{alt:"Election tool logo",contain:"",src:o("9b19"),transition:"scale-transition",width:"50","min-width":"270","min-height":"80"}})],1),i("v-spacer"),i("v-btn",{staticClass:"nav-text nav-icon-text px-5",attrs:{to:"/survey",text:""}},[i("v-icon",{staticClass:"nav-icon pr-1"},[e._v("mdi-apple-keyboard-command")]),i("span",[e._v("Tool")])],1),i("v-btn",{staticClass:"nav-text nav-icon-text px-5",attrs:{to:"/how-to-use",text:""}},[i("v-icon",{staticClass:"nav-icon pr-1"},[e._v("mdi-format-list-bulleted")]),i("span",[e._v("How To Use")])],1),"/survey"==e.$route.path?i("v-btn",{staticClass:"nav-text gen-report nav-icon-text px-5",attrs:{text:""},on:{click:function(t){return e.goToResults()}}},[i("v-icon",{staticClass:"nav-icon pr-1",attrs:{color:"white"}},[e._v("mdi-open-in-new")]),i("span",[e._v("Generate Report")])],1):e._e()],1)},d=[],h=o("dfa3");function g(e){function t(){if("undefined"===typeof Reflect||!Reflect.construct)return!1;if(Reflect.construct.sham)return!1;if("function"===typeof Proxy)return!0;try{return Date.prototype.toString.call(Reflect.construct(Date,[],(function(){}))),!0}catch(e){return!1}}return function(){var o,i=Object(p["a"])(e);if(t()){var s=Object(p["a"])(this).constructor;o=Reflect.construct(i,arguments,s)}else o=i.apply(this,arguments);return Object(u["a"])(this,o)}}var b=function(e){Object(l["a"])(o,e);var t=g(o);function o(){return Object(r["a"])(this,o),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(a["a"])(o,[{key:"goToResults",value:function(){h["a"].$emit("go-to-results")}}]),o}(m["c"]);b=Object(c["a"])([m["a"]],b);var w=b,f=w,k=(o("16a3"),o("2877")),v=o("6544"),I=o.n(v),S=o("40dc"),A=o("8336"),P=o("132d"),q=o("adda"),N=o("2fa4"),D=Object(k["a"])(f,y,d,!1,null,null,null),M=D.exports;I()(D,{VAppBar:S["a"],VBtn:A["a"],VIcon:P["a"],VImg:q["a"],VSpacer:N["a"]});var j=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,i=e._self._c||t;return i("v-footer",{attrs:{padless:""}},[i("v-card",{staticClass:"footer-container",attrs:{flat:"",tile:"",width:"100%"}},[i("v-card-text",{staticClass:"white--text"},[i("v-row",[i("v-col",{staticClass:"px-5",attrs:{cols:"3"}},[i("p",{staticClass:"version"},[e._v(e._s(e.version))]),i("p",{staticClass:"version-date my-5"},[e._v(e._s(e.versionDate))]),i("h3",{staticClass:"mb-3"},[e._v("Contact Us")]),i("p",[e._v(" Comments or questions on this tool should be addressed to the "),i("a",{attrs:{href:"mailto:EISSA@cisa.dhs.gov"}},[e._v("CISA Election Security Initiative")]),e._v(". ")]),i("img",{attrs:{src:o("40c8"),alt:"CISA Logo","aria-label":"CISA Logo"}}),i("img",{attrs:{src:o("283c"),alt:"EAC Logo","aria-label":"EAC Logo"}})]),i("v-divider",{staticClass:"my-5",attrs:{color:"black",vertical:""}}),i("v-col",{staticClass:"px-5",attrs:{cols:"5.5"}},[i("h2",{staticClass:"my-5"},[e._v("About CISA")]),i("p",[e._v(" This research was sponsored by the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) and jointly released with the US Election Assistance Commission in support of the state and local election officials, and all members of the election community, to ensure that these critical partners have the information necessary to assess and manage risk to their election infrastructure systems. This analysis builds on research performed by the HSOAC, an FFRDC operated by RAND Corporation on behalf of the Department of Homeland Security. ")]),i("p",[e._v(" The results presented in this report do not necessarily reflect official CISA opinion or policy. For more information on CISA Election Security resources, visit the "),i("a",{attrs:{target:"_blank",href:"https://www.cisa.gov/protect2020#"}},[e._v("#Protect2020")]),e._v(" page. ")])]),i("v-divider",{staticClass:"my-5",attrs:{color:"black",vertical:""}}),i("v-col",{staticClass:"px-5",attrs:{cols:"3"}},[i("h1",{staticClass:"my-6"},[e._v("License Agreement")]),i("p",{staticClass:"my-10 mr-2"},[e._v(" Use of this tool implies consent with the enclosed license agreement. ")]),i("v-btn",{staticClass:"text-center white--text",attrs:{height:"50",color:"blue"},on:{click:function(t){return e.showAgreement()}}},[i("span",{attrs:{id:"license-agreement"}},[e._v("View License Agreement")]),i("v-icon",{staticClass:"ml-4"},[e._v("mdi-information")])],1)],1)],1)],1)],1),i("InfoModal",{attrs:{modalContent:e.modalContent,name:"License Agreement",showDialog:e.licenseDialog},on:{close:function(t){e.licenseDialog=t}}})],1)},Y=[],T=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,i=e._self._c||t;return i("v-dialog",{attrs:{"max-width":"75%",scrollable:"",persistent:"License Agreement"!==e.name},model:{value:e.showDialog,callback:function(t){e.showDialog=t},expression:"showDialog"}},[i("v-card",{staticClass:"agreement",attrs:{color:"white"}},[i("v-card-text",[i("v-row",{staticClass:"ma-5 pa-5"},[i("v-col",{attrs:{cols:"2"}},[i("img",{attrs:{src:o("b3c5"),alt:"Letter i icon indicating information"}})]),i("v-col",{staticClass:"mt-4",attrs:{cols:"8"}},[i("h2",{staticClass:"mb-5 dialog-header"},[e._v(e._s(e.name))]),i("v-divider",{staticClass:"my-7",attrs:{color:"grey"}}),"License Agreement"===e.name?i("div",{staticClass:"scrollbar"},[e._l(this.modalContent,(function(t,o){return i("v-row",{key:o},[i("v-col",{attrs:{cols:"2"}},[i("p",{staticClass:"index",attrs:{color:"blue"}},[e._v(" "+e._s(t.index)+" ")])]),i("v-col",{attrs:{cols:"10"}},[i("h3",{staticClass:"mb-3"},[e._v(e._s(t.title))]),i("p",{domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(t.text)}})])],1)})),i("v-row",[i("v-col")],1)],2):e._e(),"License Agreement"!==e.name?i("div",{staticClass:"scrollbar"},[i("v-row",[i("v-col",{attrs:{cols:"1"}}),i("v-col",{attrs:{cols:"11"}},[e._v(" This tool is intended to help identify and prioritize risk to a State or Jurisdiction's election system and to identify mitigation options. ")])],1),i("br"),i("v-row",[i("v-col",{attrs:{cols:"1"}}),i("v-col",{attrs:{cols:"11"}},[i("strong",[e._v(" To use this tool, please follow these general instructions: ")])])],1),e._l(this.modalContent,(function(t,o){return i("v-row",{key:o},[i("v-col",{attrs:{cols:"1"}},[i("p",{staticClass:"index",attrs:{color:"blue"}},[e._v(" "+e._s(t.index)+" ")])]),i("v-col",{attrs:{cols:"11"}},[i("p",{domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(t.text)}}),t.subtext.length>0?i("div",{staticClass:"pl-7"},e._l(t.subtext,(function(t,o){return i("p",{key:o,domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(t.text)}})})),0):e._e()])],1)}))],2):e._e(),i("div",{staticClass:"text-center"})],1),i("v-col",{attrs:{cols:"2"}})],1)],1),i("v-card-actions",{staticClass:"justify-center card-actions mt-5"},["License Agreement"===e.name?i("v-btn",{staticClass:"mx-2 mb-2",attrs:{width:"200px",height:"50px",color:"grey white--text"},on:{click:function(t){return e.closeDialog()}}},[i("v-icon",{staticClass:"mr-3"},[e._v("mdi-close")]),e._v("Cancel ")],1):e._e(),"License Agreement"===e.name?i("a",{attrs:{href:"CISA-ESRPT-License-Agreement.pdf",download:""}},[i("v-btn",{staticClass:"mx-2 mb-2",attrs:{width:"200px",height:"50px",color:"green white--text"}},[e._v(" Download "),i("v-icon",{staticClass:"ml-3"},[e._v("mdi-download")])],1)],1):e._e(),"License Agreement"!==e.name?i("v-btn",{staticClass:"mb-2",attrs:{width:"200px",height:"50px",color:"green white--text"},on:{click:function(t){return e.closeDialog()}}},[e._v("Continue")]):e._e()],1)],1)],1)},x=[];function C(e){function t(){if("undefined"===typeof Reflect||!Reflect.construct)return!1;if(Reflect.construct.sham)return!1;if("function"===typeof Proxy)return!0;try{return Date.prototype.toString.call(Reflect.construct(Date,[],(function(){}))),!0}catch(e){return!1}}return function(){var o,i=Object(p["a"])(e);if(t()){var s=Object(p["a"])(this).constructor;o=Reflect.construct(i,arguments,s)}else o=i.apply(this,arguments);return Object(u["a"])(this,o)}}var W=function(e){Object(l["a"])(o,e);var t=C(o);function o(){return Object(r["a"])(this,o),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(a["a"])(o,[{key:"closeDialog",value:function(){this.$emit("close",!1)}}]),o}(m["c"]);Object(c["a"])([Object(m["b"])()],W.prototype,"modalContent",void 0),Object(c["a"])([Object(m["b"])()],W.prototype,"name",void 0),Object(c["a"])([Object(m["b"])()],W.prototype,"showDialog",void 0),W=Object(c["a"])([Object(m["a"])({components:{}})],W);var E=W,R=E,V=o("b0af"),_=o("99d9"),U=o("62ad"),Q=o("169a"),H=o("ce7e"),O=o("0fd9"),F=Object(k["a"])(R,T,x,!1,null,null,null),B=F.exports;function L(e){function t(){if("undefined"===typeof Reflect||!Reflect.construct)return!1;if(Reflect.construct.sham)return!1;if("function"===typeof Proxy)return!0;try{return Date.prototype.toString.call(Reflect.construct(Date,[],(function(){}))),!0}catch(e){return!1}}return function(){var o,i=Object(p["a"])(e);if(t()){var s=Object(p["a"])(this).constructor;o=Reflect.construct(i,arguments,s)}else o=i.apply(this,arguments);return Object(u["a"])(this,o)}}I()(F,{VBtn:A["a"],VCard:V["a"],VCardActions:_["a"],VCardText:_["b"],VCol:U["a"],VDialog:Q["a"],VDivider:H["a"],VIcon:P["a"],VRow:O["a"]});var G=function(e){Object(l["a"])(o,e);var t=L(o);function o(){var e;return Object(r["a"])(this,o),e=t.apply(this,arguments),e.version="Version 1.1",e.versionDate="July, 2020",e.licenseDialog=!1,e.modalContent=[{index:1,title:"Intellectual Property Rights and Uses",text:"Copyright and other intellectual property laws protect <strong>Election  Security  Risk  Profile  Tool (ESRPT).</strong> Intellectual property rights in <strong>ESRPT</strong> belong to the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency to the greatest extent allowed by law. <strong>ESRPT</strong> was developed under the sponsorship of the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency and has been provided for use in compliance with applicable laws and regulations."},{index:2,title:"Disclaimer of Consequential Damages",text:"Under no circumstances shall CISA be liable for any consequential or incidental damages whatsoever arising out of the use of <strong>ESPRT</strong> or inability to use the tool, including without limitation, computer failure, work stoppage or any other damages, even if CISA has been advised of the possibility of such damages. <strong>ESRPT</strong> was developed to support specific analysis demands. Proper use requires care and subject matter expertise. Computer code associated with <strong>ESRPT</strong> has not been the subject of detailed verification, validation, or accreditation. CISA provides  this  tool  with  no  warranty  and  is  under  no  obligation  to  provide  additional documentation or training. Use of this tool does not imply that analytical results obtained by the user are sanctioned by CISA."},{index:3,title:"General Terms",text:"All applicable federal laws and regulations govern this agreement. If any provision of this agreement is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of this agreement, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any term of this agreement shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or any other term. This agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and CISA with respect to this transaction. Any changes to this agreement must be made in writing, signed by an authorized representative of CISA."}],e}return Object(a["a"])(o,[{key:"showAgreement",value:function(){this.licenseDialog=!0}}]),o}(m["c"]);G=Object(c["a"])([Object(m["a"])({components:{InfoModal:B}})],G);var z=G,J=z,$=(o("53d7"),o("553a")),K=Object(k["a"])(J,j,Y,!1,null,null,null),X=K.exports;I()(K,{VBtn:A["a"],VCard:V["a"],VCardText:_["b"],VCol:U["a"],VDivider:H["a"],VFooter:$["a"],VIcon:P["a"],VRow:O["a"]});var Z=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("v-container",{staticClass:"mobile-home d-flex justify-center align-center",attrs:{fluid:"","fill-height":""}},[o("h1",{staticClass:"text-center"},[e._v(" Election Security Tool performs best on Desktops and Laptops ")])])},ee=[],te={},oe=te,ie=(o("7e11"),o("a523")),se=Object(k["a"])(oe,Z,ee,!1,null,null,null),ne=se.exports;function re(e){function t(){if("undefined"===typeof Reflect||!Reflect.construct)return!1;if(Reflect.construct.sham)return!1;if("function"===typeof Proxy)return!0;try{return Date.prototype.toString.call(Reflect.construct(Date,[],(function(){}))),!0}catch(e){return!1}}return function(){var o,i=Object(p["a"])(e);if(t()){var s=Object(p["a"])(this).constructor;o=Reflect.construct(i,arguments,s)}else o=i.apply(this,arguments);return Object(u["a"])(this,o)}}I()(se,{VContainer:ie["a"]});var ae=function(e){Object(l["a"])(o,e);var t=re(o);function o(){var e;return Object(r["a"])(this,o),e=t.apply(this,arguments),e.ie=null,e.ie11=null,e}return Object(a["a"])(o,[{key:"mounted",value:function(){this.ie=navigator.userAgent.match(/MSIE\s([\d.]+)/),this.ie11=navigator.userAgent.match(/Trident\/7.0/)&&navigator.userAgent.match(/rv:11/),(this.ie11||this.ie)&&this.$store.commit("setIsIE",!0)}}]),o}(m["c"]);ae=Object(c["a"])([Object(m["a"])({components:{Navbar:M,Footer:X,MobileWarning:ne},methods:{isMobile:function(){return window.innerWidth<=760}}})],ae);var le=ae,ue=le,pe=(o("5c0b"),o("7496")),ce=o("a75b"),me=Object(k["a"])(ue,s,n,!1,null,null,null),ye=me.exports;I()(me,{VApp:pe["a"],VContent:ce["a"]});o("b0c0");var de=o("8c4f"),he=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,i=e._self._c||t;return i("v-container",{staticClass:"pa-0 ma-0 home-container",attrs:{fluid:"","fill-height":""}},[i("v-row",{staticClass:"home-row",class:{"force-height":!e.$vuetify.breakpoint.xs},attrs:{align:"center",justify:"center"}},[i("v-col",{staticClass:"upload-col text-center",attrs:{xs:"12",sm:"6",align:"center"}},[i("v-row",{staticClass:"upload-content",attrs:{"align-content":"center",justify:"center"}},[i("v-col",[i("v-flex",[i("img",{staticClass:"mx-auto my-10 d-flex",attrs:{"max-width":"80px",src:o("e162"),alt:"Icon indicating that files can be uploaded"}}),i("img",{staticClass:"mx-auto my-5 d-flex",attrs:{"max-width":"400px",src:o("ad4b"),alt:"Upload answers text"}}),i("FileUpload",{staticClass:"my-10 mx-auto",on:{change:e.uploadData,resume:function(t){return e.setUpSavedVariables()}}})],1)],1)],1)],1),i("v-col",{staticClass:"text-center",attrs:{xs:"12",sm:"6"}},[i("v-row",{staticClass:"new-survey-content",attrs:{"align-content":"center",justify:"center"}},[i("v-col",[i("v-flex",[i("img",{attrs:{src:o("0462"),alt:"Begin new survey text"}}),i("h2",{staticClass:"mb-10 survey-text"},[i("strong",[e._v("Begin New")]),e._v(" Survey ")]),i("v-btn",{staticClass:"new-survey white--text",attrs:{height:"65",color:"blue"},on:{click:function(t){return e.newSurvey()}}},[i("span",{staticClass:"ml-2"},[e._v("New Survey")]),i("v-icon",{staticClass:"ml-8 mr-1"},[e._v("mdi-plus")])],1)],1)],1)],1)],1)],1),i("v-dialog",{attrs:{"max-width":"290"},model:{value:e.errorDialog,callback:function(t){e.errorDialog=t},expression:"errorDialog"}},[i("v-card",[i("v-card-title",{staticClass:"headline"},[i("v-icon",{staticClass:"mr-2",attrs:{color:"danger"}},[e._v("mdi-alert-outline")]),e._v("Invalid File ")],1),i("v-card-text",{staticClass:"pt-5"},[i("p",{staticClass:"justify-left"},[e._v(" There is a problem with the file you have uploaded. Upload a different file or start a new session. ")]),i("v-expansion-panels",[i("v-expansion-panel",[i("v-expansion-panel-header",[e._v("View Errors")]),i("v-expansion-panel-content",[e._v(" "+e._s(e.errors)+" ")])],1)],1)],1),i("v-card-actions",{staticClass:"px-5 pb-4"},[i("v-spacer"),i("v-btn",{staticClass:"white--text pl-5",attrs:{color:"red"},on:{click:function(t){e.errorDialog=!1}}},[e._v(" Dismiss "),i("v-icon",{staticClass:"ml-2"},[e._v("mdi-close")])],1)],1)],1)],1),i("v-dialog",{attrs:{"max-width":"50%"},model:{value:e.newSurveyDialog,callback:function(t){e.newSurveyDialog=t},expression:"newSurveyDialog"}},[i("v-card",[i("v-card-title",{staticClass:"headline"},[i("v-icon",{staticClass:"mr-2",attrs:{color:"danger"}},[e._v("mdi-alert-outline")]),e._v("Existing Survey in Progress ")],1),i("v-card-text",{staticClass:"pt-5"},[i("p",{staticClass:"justify-left"},[e._v(" You have already started a survey. Do you want to start over? ")])]),i("v-card-actions",{staticClass:"px-5 pb-4"},[i("v-btn",{staticClass:"white--text pr-5",attrs:{color:"red"},on:{click:function(t){return e.startNewSurvey()}}},[i("v-icon",{staticClass:"mr-2"},[e._v("mdi-check")]),e._v("Yes, Start New Survey ")],1),i("v-spacer"),i("v-btn",{staticClass:"white--text pl-5",attrs:{color:"blue",to:{name:"Survey"}}},[e._v(" No, Resume Existing Survey "),i("v-icon",{staticClass:"ml-2"},[e._v("mdi-cancel")])],1)],1)],1)],1),i("InfoModal",{attrs:{name:"Using This Tool",showDialog:e.infoDialog,modalContent:e.infoModalContent},on:{close:function(t){return e.goToSurvey(t)}}})],1)},ge=[],be=(o("99af"),o("257e")),we=o("ade3"),fe=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("div",{class:{"with-button":e.touched},attrs:{id:"file-upload-container"}},[o("form",{staticClass:"form"},[o("label",{staticClass:"custom-file-upload text-center",class:{"file-selected":e.touched,highlight:e.hovereffect},attrs:{for:"file-upload"}},[o("span",{staticClass:"imported",class:{"d-none":!e.touched}},[o("v-icon",{staticClass:"my-3",attrs:{size:"30",color:"green"}},[e._v("mdi-file-document-outline")])],1),o("span",{class:{placeholder:!e.touched,"file-selected":e.touched,highlight:e.hovereffect},attrs:{id:"file-upload-filename"}},[e.touched?o("span",[e._v(e._s(e.fileName))]):e._e(),e.touched?e._e():o("span",[e.isIE?e._e():o("span",{staticClass:"not-ie"},[e._v("Drag and Drop or Browse Files")]),e.isIE?o("span",{staticClass:"is-ie"},[e._v("Click to Browse Files")]):e._e()])]),o("br"),e.touched?o("v-btn",{staticClass:"my-3",attrs:{id:"remove",text:""},on:{click:function(t){return e.removeButtonClick(t)}}},[o("v-icon",{class:{"d-none":!e.touched},attrs:{color:"white"}},[e._v("mdi-close")])],1):e._e(),o("input",{attrs:{id:"file-upload",name:"file-upload",type:"file",accept:".txt"},on:{change:e.sendFileToParent}})],1),o("div",{staticClass:"text-center"},[o("v-btn",{staticClass:"blue--text mt-5",class:{"d-none":!e.touched},attrs:{height:"50",name:"Resume survey button",type:"button"},on:{click:function(t){return e.resumeEmit()}}},[e._v(" Resume Survey "),o("v-icon",{staticClass:"ml-3",attrs:{color:"blue"}},[e._v("mdi-file-account-outline")])],1)],1)])])},ke=[];o("1276");function ve(e){function t(){if("undefined"===typeof Reflect||!Reflect.construct)return!1;if(Reflect.construct.sham)return!1;if("function"===typeof Proxy)return!0;try{return Date.prototype.toString.call(Reflect.construct(Date,[],(function(){}))),!0}catch(e){return!1}}return function(){var o,i=Object(p["a"])(e);if(t()){var s=Object(p["a"])(this).constructor;o=Reflect.construct(i,arguments,s)}else o=i.apply(this,arguments);return Object(u["a"])(this,o)}}var Ie=function(e){Object(l["a"])(o,e);var t=ve(o);function o(){var e;return Object(r["a"])(this,o),e=t.apply(this,arguments),e.input=null,e.infoArea=null,e.fileName=null,e.touched=!1,e.removeButton=null,e.dropArea=null,e.hovereffect=!1,e}return Object(a["a"])(o,[{key:"mounted",value:function(){this.input=document.getElementById("file-upload"),this.infoArea=document.getElementById("file-upload-filename"),this.dropArea=document.getElementById("file-upload-container"),null!=this.input&&this.input.addEventListener("change",this.showFileName),null!=this.dropArea&&(this.dropArea.addEventListener("dragenter",this.highlight,!1),this.dropArea.addEventListener("dragleave",this.unHighlight,!1),this.dropArea.addEventListener("dragover",this.highlight,!1),this.dropArea.addEventListener("drop",this.drop,!1))}},{key:"showFileName",value:function(){if(null!=this.input&&null!=this.input.files&&(this.fileName=this.input.files[0].name),null!=this.fileName){var e=this.fileName.split(".").pop();null!=this.infoArea&&(this.touched=!0),"txt"!==e&&(alert("You can only import text files ('.txt') in this section."),this.removeFile())}}},{key:"removeButtonClick",value:function(e){e.preventDefault(),e.stopPropagation(),this.removeFile()}},{key:"removeFile",value:function(){null!=this.infoArea&&null!=this.input&&(this.input.value="",this.touched=!1,this.sendFileToParent())}},{key:"preventDefaults",value:function(e){e.preventDefault(),e.stopPropagation()}},{key:"highlight",value:function(e){this.preventDefaults(e),this.hovereffect=!0}},{key:"drop",value:function(e){null!=this.input&&null!=e.dataTransfer&&(this.preventDefaults(e),this.input.files=e.dataTransfer.files,this.hovereffect=!1,this.showFileName(),this.sendFileToParent())}},{key:"unHighlight",value:function(e){this.preventDefaults(e),this.hovereffect=!1}},{key:"sendFileToParent",value:function(){null!=this.input&&this.$emit("change",this.input.files)}},{key:"resumeEmit",value:function(){this.$emit("resume")}},{key:"isIE",get:function(){return this.$store.getters.isIE}}]),o}(m["c"]);Ie=Object(c["a"])([m["a"]],Ie);var Se,Ae,Pe,qe=Ie,Ne=qe,De=(o("2a01"),Object(k["a"])(Ne,fe,ke,!1,null,"e1e2bf3a",null)),Me=De.exports;function je(e){function t(){if("undefined"===typeof Reflect||!Reflect.construct)return!1;if(Reflect.construct.sham)return!1;if("function"===typeof Proxy)return!0;try{return Date.prototype.toString.call(Reflect.construct(Date,[],(function(){}))),!0}catch(e){return!1}}return function(){var o,i=Object(p["a"])(e);if(t()){var s=Object(p["a"])(this).constructor;o=Reflect.construct(i,arguments,s)}else o=i.apply(this,arguments);return Object(u["a"])(this,o)}}I()(De,{VBtn:A["a"],VIcon:P["a"]});var Ye=(Se=Object(m["a"])({components:{FileUpload:Me,InfoModal:B}}),Se((Pe=function(e){Object(l["a"])(i,e);var t=je(i);function i(){var e;Object(r["a"])(this,i);for(var s=arguments.length,n=new Array(s),a=0;a<s;a++)n[a]=arguments[a];return e=t.call.apply(t,[this].concat(n)),Object(we["a"])(Object(be["a"])(e),"errorDialog",!1),Object(we["a"])(Object(be["a"])(e),"newSurveyDialog",!1),Object(we["a"])(Object(be["a"])(e),"infoDialog",!1),Object(we["a"])(Object(be["a"])(e),"errors",null),Object(we["a"])(Object(be["a"])(e),"Ajv",o("783b")),Object(we["a"])(Object(be["a"])(e),"schema",null),Object(we["a"])(Object(be["a"])(e),"ajv",new e.Ajv),Object(we["a"])(Object(be["a"])(e),"resetData",null),Object(we["a"])(Object(be["a"])(e),"importedData",null),Object(we["a"])(Object(be["a"])(e),"infoModalContent",[{index:1,text:"You should navigate through each of the ten (10) component pages of the election system, answering all available questions to the best of your ability on each page.",subtext:[{text:" While the order that the components are listed is intentional, <strong>users may populate sections in any order</strong> and may jump around from section to section as necessary. The left-hand progress menu will display progress towards completion."}]},{index:2,text:"Each component has multiple sections containing Yes/No and Short-Answer questions about various election security components. This may require consultation with your local system administrators, cybersecurity professionals, and other IT staff.",subtext:[{text:"Across pages, <strong>tool-tips</strong> are utilized to provide the user with definitions and clarifications, and users may input <strong>comments/notes</strong> on any question to add context or justification for scores."},{text:"A <strong>bookmarking capability</strong> exists for each question in the tool reminding users to return to the specific question later."},{text:"Many of the provided answers may default the answer to subsequent questions. <strong>Logic is built into the tool</strong> to ensure there is consistency and accuracy in responses."}]},{index:3,text:"Responses across components are transferred to the 'Risk Profile' report which provides an overview of the component's high priority risk areas, as well as overall order of risks. It also identifies specific risk-mitigations and suggested services based on the user's responses. Finally, all components are organized into a risk order. The risk order should not be taken as a quantitative measure of risk, but rather as a means of prioritizing risks across components with similar risk assessments.",subtext:[{text:"Note: Results will be generated even if there are unanswered questions or unpopulated component sections. "}]}]),e}return Object(a["a"])(i,[{key:"uploadData",value:function(e){var t=this;if(e.length<=0)return!1;var o=new FileReader;o.onload=function(e){var o=JSON.parse(e.target.result);t.importedData=o},o.readAsText(e.item(0))}},{key:"newSurvey",value:function(){this.surveyTouched?this.newSurveyDialog=!0:this.infoDialog=!0}},{key:"goToSurvey",value:function(e){this.infoDialog=!1,this.$router.push("/survey")}},{key:"startNewSurvey",value:function(){this.newSurveyDialog=!1,this.resetData=o("45cd"),this.importedData=JSON.parse(JSON.stringify(this.resetData)),this.setUpSavedVariables()}},{key:"setUpSavedVariables",value:function(){this.schema=o("93ad");var e=this.ajv.compile(this.schema),t=e(this.importedData);t||(this.errors=JSON.stringify(e.errors),this.errorDialog=!0),t&&(this.$store.commit("setVoterRegistrationQuestions",this.importedData.voterRegistrationQuestions),this.$store.commit("setPollbookPrepQuestions",this.importedData.pollbookPrepQuestions),this.$store.commit("setPollbookUseQuestions",this.importedData.pollbookUseQuestions),this.$store.commit("setBallotPrepQuestions",this.importedData.ballotPrepQuestions),this.$store.commit("setVotingMachinePrepQuestions",this.importedData.votingMachinePrepQuestions),this.$store.commit("setVotingMachineUseQuestions",this.importedData.votingMachineUseQuestions),this.$store.commit("setTabulationPrepQuestions",this.importedData.tabulationPrepQuestions),this.$store.commit("setPrecinctTabulationQuestions",this.importedData.precinctTabulationQuestions),this.$store.commit("setCentralTabulationQuestions",this.importedData.centralTabulationQuestions),this.$store.commit("setAggregationQuestions",this.importedData.aggregationQuestions),this.$store.commit("setWebsiteQuestions",this.importedData.websiteQuestions),this.$store.commit("setVoterRegistrationVisited",this.importedData.voterRegistrationVisited),this.$store.commit("setPollbookPrepVisited",this.importedData.pollbookPrepVisited),this.$store.commit("setPollbookUseVisited",this.importedData.pollbookUseVisited),this.$store.commit("setBallotPrepVisited",this.importedData.ballotPrepVisited),this.$store.commit("setVotingMachinePrepVisited",this.importedData.votingMachinePrepVisited),this.$store.commit("setVotingMachineUseVisited",this.importedData.votingMachineUseVisited),this.$store.commit("setTabulationPrepVisited",this.importedData.tabulationPrepVisited),this.$store.commit("setPrecinctTabulationVisited",this.importedData.precinctTabulationVisited),this.$store.commit("setCentralTabulationVisited",this.importedData.centralTabulationVisited),this.$store.commit("setAggregationVisited",this.importedData.aggregationVisited),this.$store.commit("setWebsiteVisited",this.importedData.websiteVisited),this.$router.push("/survey"))}},{key:"surveyTouched",get:function(){return this.$store.getters.surveyTouched}}]),i}(m["c"]),Ae=Pe))||Ae),Te=Ye,xe=(o("21bb"),o("cd55")),Ce=o("49e2"),We=o("c865"),Ee=o("0393"),Re=o("0e8f"),Ve=Object(k["a"])(Te,he,ge,!1,null,null,null),_e=Ve.exports;I()(Ve,{VBtn:A["a"],VCard:V["a"],VCardActions:_["a"],VCardText:_["b"],VCardTitle:_["c"],VCol:U["a"],VContainer:ie["a"],VDialog:Q["a"],VExpansionPanel:xe["a"],VExpansionPanelContent:Ce["a"],VExpansionPanelHeader:We["a"],VExpansionPanels:Ee["a"],VFlex:Re["a"],VIcon:P["a"],VRow:O["a"],VSpacer:N["a"]}),i["a"].use(de["a"]);var Ue=[{path:"/",name:"Home",component:_e},{path:"/how-to-use",name:"howToUse",component:function(){return o.e("chunk-497ef5ee").then(o.bind(null,"65cc"))}},{path:"/survey",name:"Survey",component:function(){return Promise.all([o.e("risk-prioritization~survey"),o.e("survey")]).then(o.bind(null,"57e1"))}},{path:"/risk-prioritization",name:"riskPrioritization",meta:{scrollToTop:!0},component:function(){return Promise.all([o.e("risk-prioritization~survey"),o.e("risk-prioritization")]).then(o.bind(null,"22dd"))}}],Qe=new de["a"]({mode:"history",base:"/app/esa/",routes:Ue,scrollBehavior:function(e,t,o){return e.hash?{selector:e.hash}:{x:0,y:0}}}),He=de["a"].prototype.push;de["a"].prototype.push=function(e){return He.call(this,e).catch((function(e){if(void 0!=e&&"NavigationDuplicated"!==e.name)throw e}))};var Oe=Qe,Fe=o("2f62"),Be={state:{surveyTouched:!1,isIE:!1},getters:{surveyTouched:function(e){return e.surveyTouched},isIE:function(e){return e.isIE}},mutations:{setSurveyTouched:function(e,t){e.surveyTouched=t},setIsIE:function(e,t){e.isIE=t}},actions:{}},Le={state:{voterRegistrationVisited:!1,pollbookPrepVisited:!1,pollbookUseVisited:!1,ballotPrepVisited:!1,votingMachinePrepVisited:!1,votingMachineUseVisited:!1,tabulationPrepVisited:!1,precinctTabulationVisited:!1,centralTabulationVisited:!1,aggregationVisited:!1,websiteVisited:!1},getters:{voterRegistrationVisited:function(e){return e.voterRegistrationVisited},pollbookPrepVisited:function(e){return e.pollbookPrepVisited},pollbookUseVisited:function(e){return e.pollbookUseVisited},ballotPrepVisited:function(e){return e.ballotPrepVisited},votingMachinePrepVisited:function(e){return e.votingMachinePrepVisited},votingMachineUseVisited:function(e){return e.votingMachineUseVisited},tabulationPrepVisited:function(e){return e.tabulationPrepVisited},precinctTabulationVisited:function(e){return e.precinctTabulationVisited},centralTabulationVisited:function(e){return e.centralTabulationVisited},aggregationVisited:function(e){return e.aggregationVisited},websiteVisited:function(e){return e.websiteVisited}},mutations:{setVoterRegistrationVisited:function(e,t){e.voterRegistrationVisited=t},setPollbookPrepVisited:function(e,t){e.pollbookPrepVisited=t},setPollbookUseVisited:function(e,t){e.pollbookUseVisited=t},setBallotPrepVisited:function(e,t){e.ballotPrepVisited=t},setVotingMachinePrepVisited:function(e,t){e.votingMachinePrepVisited=t},setVotingMachineUseVisited:function(e,t){e.votingMachineUseVisited=t},setTabulationPrepVisited:function(e,t){e.tabulationPrepVisited=t},setPrecinctTabulationVisited:function(e,t){e.precinctTabulationVisited=t},setCentralTabulationVisited:function(e,t){e.centralTabulationVisited=t},setAggregationVisited:function(e,t){e.aggregationVisited=t},setWebsiteVisited:function(e,t){e.websiteVisited=t}}},Ge={state:{voterRegistrationQuestions:{scaleQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Scale of Voter Registration Database (VRDB)",sectionId:1,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{jurisdictionOrState:{question:"Is the database managed at the Jurisdiction or State level?",options:["Jurisdiction","State"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"jurisdictionOrState",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},scale:{question:"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.",options:["High","Medium","Low"],type:"dropdown",show:!1,id:"scale",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},tooltip:"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},accessQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Access to Voter Registration Database (VRDB)",sectionId:2,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{remoteAccess:{question:"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"remoteAccess",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},remoteAccessNoAuth:{question:"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"remoteAccessNoAuth",mitigation:null,tooltip:"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},anyIPS:{question:"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"anyIPS",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System",service:"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B",tooltip:"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},allowList:{question:"Do you add IPs to the 'Allow List'?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"allowList",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses",service:"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy",source:"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf",tooltip:"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},proximateAccess:{question:"Is there proximate access to the system?",tooltip:"Proximate access refers to 'Bluetooth' and 'Wifi'.",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"proximateAccess",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},bluetooth:{question:"Is Bluetooth enabled?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"bluetooth",mitigation:null,tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wifi:{question:"Is there WiFi access?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wifi",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wepOrWpa1:{question:"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wepOrWpa1",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wpa2:{question:"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wpa2",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},physicalMedia:{question:"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"physicalMedia",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},removableMediaPolicy:{question:"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"removableMediaPolicy",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Enact removable media policy",service:"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf",tooltip:"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},authQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Authentication",sectionId:3,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{anyAuth:{question:"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"anyAuth",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},sfa:{question:"Do you use single factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"sfa",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},mfa:{question:"Do you use multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"mfa",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},tfa:{question:"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"tfa",mitigation:"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet",source:"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf",tooltip:"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},ofa:{question:"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"ofa",mitigation:null,tooltip:"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},hardwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Hardware Management",sectionId:4,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.",questions:{patchHardware:{question:"Do you patch the voter registration database server?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"patchHardware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},patchHardwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the server more frequently than once per election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"patchHardwareElection",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},softwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Software Management",sectionId:5,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.",questions:{patchSoftware:{question:"Do you patch your application software for the voter registration database?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"patchSoftware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},patchSoftwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the software more frequently than once per election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"patchSoftwareElection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},ddosQuestions:{sectionTitle:"DDoS Protection",sectionId:6,complete:!1,tooltip:"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.",questions:{ddosProtection:{question:"Do you have DDoS protection for your server?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"ddosProtection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Implement DDoS protection",service:"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},importanceQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Importance Values",sectionId:7,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{confidentiality:{type:"slider",default:3.3,question:"Confidentiality",id:"confidentiality",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.3,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},integrity:{type:"slider",default:4.8,question:"Integrity",id:"integrity",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:4.8,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},availability:{type:"slider",default:3.5,question:"Availability",id:"availability",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.5,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},additionalInformation:{sectionTitle:"Additional Information",sectionId:8,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{vrComment1:{id:"vrComment-1",type:"text",question:"Are you a state or local election official?",show:!0,userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1}},vrComment2:{id:"vrComment-2",type:"text",question:"Who maintains the Voter Registration Database (VRDB) software and security?",tooltip:"For information to determine your voter database configuration, go to: https://www.eac.gov/statewide-voter-registration-systems",show:!0,userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1}},vrComment3:{id:"vrComment-3",type:"text",question:"What is the name of the Voter Registration Database (VRDB) vendor and service provider?",show:!0,userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1}},vrComment4:{id:"vrComment-4",type:"text",question:"What software is used (operating system, applications, web servers, databases)?",show:!0,userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1}},vrComment5:{id:"vrComment-5",type:"text",question:"What interconnections exist between the Voter Registration Database (VRDB) and other systems (e.g. Department of Motor Vehicles)?",show:!0,userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1}}}}}},getters:{voterRegistrationQuestions:function(e){return e.voterRegistrationQuestions}},mutations:{setVoterRegistrationQuestions:function(e,t){e.voterRegistrationQuestions=t}},actions:{}},ze={state:{pollbookPrepQuestions:{scaleQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Scale of Pollbook Preparation",sectionId:1,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{jurisdictionOrState:{question:"Is the preparation done at the Jurisdiction or State level?",options:["Jurisdiction","State"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"jurisdictionOrState",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},scale:{question:"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.",options:["High","Medium","Low"],type:"dropdown",show:!1,id:"scale",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},tooltip:"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},accessQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Access to Pollbook Preparation System",sectionId:2,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{remoteAccess:{question:"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"remoteAccess",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},remoteAccessNoAuth:{question:"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"remoteAccessNoAuth",mitigation:null,tooltip:"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},anyIPS:{question:"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"anyIPS",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System",service:"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B",tooltip:"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},allowList:{question:"Do you add IPs to the 'Allow List'?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"allowList",mitigation:"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses",service:"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy",source:"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf",tooltip:"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},proximateAccess:{question:"Is there proximate access to the system?",tooltip:"Proximate access refers to 'Bluetooth' and 'Wifi'.",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"proximateAccess",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},bluetooth:{question:"Is Bluetooth enabled?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"bluetooth",mitigation:null,tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wifi:{question:"Is there WiFi access?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wifi",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wepOrWpa1:{question:"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wepOrWpa1",mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wpa2:{question:"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",showMitigation:!1,show:!1,id:"wpa2",mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},physicalMedia:{question:"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"physicalMedia",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},removableMediaPolicy:{question:"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",showMitigation:!1,show:!1,id:"removableMediaPolicy",mitigation:"Enact removable media policy",service:"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf",tooltip:"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},authQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Authentication",sectionId:3,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{anyAuth:{question:"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,showMitigation:!1,id:"anyAuth",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},sfa:{question:"Do you use single factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"sfa",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},mfa:{question:"Do you use multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"mfa"},tfa:{question:"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",showMitigation:!1,show:!1,id:"tfa",mitigation:"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet",source:"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf",tooltip:"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},ofa:{question:"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"ofa",mitigation:null,tooltip:"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},hardwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Hardware Management",sectionId:4,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.",questions:{patchHardware:{question:"Do you patch the system used for pollbook preparation?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",showMitigation:!1,show:!0,id:"patchHardware",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},patchHardwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the system prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"patchHardwareElection",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},softwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Software Management",sectionId:5,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.",questions:{patchSoftware:{question:"Do you patch your application software used to prepare pollbooks?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",showMitigation:!1,show:!0,id:"patchSoftware",mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},patchSoftwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the software prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"patchSoftwareElection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},ddosQuestions:{sectionTitle:"DDoS Protection",sectionId:6,complete:!1,tooltip:"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.",questions:{ddosProtection:{question:"Do you have DDoS protection for your server?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",showMitigation:!1,show:!0,id:"ddosProtection",mitigation:"Implement DDoS protection",service:"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},importanceQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Importance Values",color:"white",sectionId:7,complete:!0,comments:null,tooltip:null,questions:{confidentiality:{type:"slider",default:2.7,question:"Confidentiality",id:"confidentiality",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:2.7,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},integrity:{type:"slider",default:3.8,question:"Integrity",id:"integrity",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.8,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},availability:{type:"slider",default:3.1,question:"Availability",id:"availability",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.1,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},additionalInformation:{sectionTitle:"Additional Information",color:"white",sectionId:8,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{pbComment1:{id:"pbComment-1",type:"text",question:"Who is the pollbook prepared by?",show:!0,userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1}},pbComment2:{id:"pbComment-2",type:"text",question:"Who manages pollbook preparation? (Local Jurisdiction, State, or vendor)",show:!0,userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1}},pbComment3:{id:"pbComment-3",type:"text",question:"What is the name, make, and model of the System used to prepare the pollbook?",show:!0,userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1}}}}}},getters:{pollbookPrepQuestions:function(e){return e.pollbookPrepQuestions}},mutations:{setPollbookPrepQuestions:function(e,t){e.pollbookPrepQuestions=t}},actions:{}},Je={state:{pollbookUseQuestions:{scaleQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Scale of Pollbook Use",sectionId:1,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{networkedOrNonNetworked:{question:"Is the pollbook networked or non-networked?",options:["Networked","Non-Networked"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"networkedOrNonNetworked"},jurisdictionOrState:{question:"Is the pollbook used at the Jurisdiction or State level?",options:["Jurisdiction","State"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"jurisdictionOrState"},scale:{question:"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.",options:["High","Medium","Low"],type:"dropdown",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"scale",tooltip:"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},accessQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Access to Pollbook",sectionId:2,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{remoteAccess:{question:"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"remoteAccess"},remoteAccessNoAuth:{question:"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"remoteAccessNoAuth",mitigation:null,tooltip:"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},anyIPS:{question:"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"anyIPS",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System",service:"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B",tooltip:"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity."},allowList:{question:"Do you add IPs to the 'Allow List'?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"allowList",mitigation:"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses",service:"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy",source:"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf",tooltip:"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses."},proximateAccess:{question:"Is there proximate access to the system?",tooltip:"Proximate access refers to 'Bluetooth' and 'Wifi'.",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"proximateAccess"},bluetooth:{question:"Is Bluetooth enabled?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"bluetooth",mitigation:null,tooltip:null},wifi:{question:"Is there WiFi access?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wifi",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,tooltip:null},wepOrWpa1:{question:"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wepOrWpa1",mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks."},wpa2:{question:"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},showMitigation:!1,show:!1,id:"wpa2",mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP."},physicalMedia:{question:"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"physicalMedia"},removableMediaPolicy:{question:"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},showMitigation:!1,show:!1,id:"removableMediaPolicy",mitigation:"Enact removable media policy",service:"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf",tooltip:"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question."}}},authQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Authentication",sectionId:3,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{anyAuth:{question:"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,showMitigation:!1,id:"anyAuth",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},sfa:{question:"Do you use single factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"sfa",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},mfa:{question:"Do you use multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"mfa"},tfa:{question:"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},showMitigation:!1,show:!1,id:"tfa",mitigation:"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet",source:"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf",tooltip:"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”."},ofa:{question:"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"ofa",mitigation:null,tooltip:"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator"}}},hardwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Hardware Management",sectionId:4,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.",questions:{patchHardware:{question:"Do you keep the pollbook system updated and patched?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},showMitigation:!1,show:!0,id:"patchHardware",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null},patchHardwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the system prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"patchHardwareElection",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null}}},softwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Software Management",sectionId:5,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.",questions:{patchSoftware:{question:"Do you patch your pollbook application software?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},showMitigation:!1,show:!0,id:"patchSoftware",mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/"},patchSoftwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the software prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"patchSoftwareElection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null}}},ddosQuestions:{sectionTitle:"DDoS Protection",sectionId:6,complete:!1,tooltip:"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.",questions:{ddosProtection:{question:"Do you have DDoS protection for your server?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},showMitigation:!1,show:!0,id:"ddosProtection",mitigation:"Implement DDoS protection",service:"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf"}}},importanceQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Importance Values",sectionId:7,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{confidentiality:{type:"slider",default:2.7,question:"Confidentiality",id:"confidentiality",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:2.7,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},integrity:{type:"slider",default:3.8,question:"Integrity",id:"integrity",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.8,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},availability:{type:"slider",default:3.1,question:"Availability",id:"availability",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.1,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}}}},getters:{pollbookUseQuestions:function(e){return e.pollbookUseQuestions}},mutations:{setPollbookUseQuestions:function(e,t){e.pollbookUseQuestions=t}},actions:{}},$e={state:{ballotPrepQuestions:{scaleQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Scale of Ballot Preparation",sectionId:1,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{jurisdictionOrState:{question:"Is the preparation done at the Jurisdiction or State level?",options:["Jurisdiction","State"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"jurisdictionOrState",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},scale:{question:"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.",tooltip:"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>",options:["High","Medium","Low"],type:"dropdown",show:!1,id:"scale",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},accessQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Access to the Ballot Preparation System",sectionId:2,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{remoteAccess:{question:"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"remoteAccess",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},remoteAccessNoAuth:{question:"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"remoteAccessNoAuth",mitigation:null,tooltip:"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},anyIPS:{question:"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"anyIPS",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System",service:"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B",tooltip:"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},allowList:{question:"Do you add IPs to the 'Allow List'?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"allowList",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses",service:"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy",source:"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf",tooltip:"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},ballotLoading:{question:"Do you transmit ballot definition files using an external network (e.g. VPN, internet, or web portal)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"ballotLoading",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,service:null,source:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},proximateAccess:{question:"Is there proximate access to the system?",tooltip:"Proximate access refers to 'Bluetooth' and 'Wifi'.",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"proximateAccess",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},bluetooth:{question:"Is Bluetooth enabled?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"bluetooth",mitigation:null,tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wifi:{question:"Is there WiFi access?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wifi",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wepOrWpa1:{question:"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wepOrWpa1",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wpa2:{question:"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wpa2",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},physicalMedia:{question:"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"physicalMedia",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},removableMediaPolicy:{question:"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"removableMediaPolicy",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Enact removable media policy",service:"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf",tooltip:"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},authQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Authentication",sectionId:3,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{anyAuth:{question:"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"anyAuth",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},sfa:{question:"Do you use single factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"sfa",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},mfa:{question:"Do you use multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"mfa",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},tfa:{question:"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"tfa",mitigation:"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet",source:"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf",tooltip:"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},ofa:{question:"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"ofa",mitigation:null,tooltip:"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},hardwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Hardware Management",sectionId:4,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.",questions:{patchHardware:{question:"Do you patch the system used to prepare the ballot?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"patchHardware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:"Ballot preparation systems may include ballot layout and generation software.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},patchHardwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the system prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"patchHardwareElection",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},softwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Software Management",sectionId:5,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.",questions:{patchSoftware:{question:"Do you patch your ballot preparation software?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"patchSoftware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},patchSoftwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the software prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"patchSoftwareElection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},ddosQuestions:{sectionTitle:"DDoS Protection",sectionId:6,complete:!1,tooltip:"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.",questions:{ddosProtection:{question:"Do you have DDoS protection for the system used for ballot preparation?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"ddosProtection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Implement DDoS protection",service:"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},importanceQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Importance Values",sectionId:7,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{confidentiality:{type:"slider",default:2.9,question:"Confidentiality",id:"confidentiality",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:2.9,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},integrity:{type:"slider",default:4.9,question:"Integrity",id:"integrity",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:4.9,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},availability:{type:"slider",default:3.6,question:"Availability",id:"availability",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.6,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},additionalInformation:{sectionTitle:"Additional Information",sectionId:8,complete:!0,questions:{bpComment1:{id:"bpComment-1",type:"text",question:"Who manages ballot preparation? (Local Jurisdiction, State, or vendor)",show:!0,userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1}},bpComment2:{id:"bpComment-2",type:"text",question:"What is the name, make, and model of the System used to prepare ballots?",show:!0,userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1}}}}}},getters:{ballotPrepQuestions:function(e){return e.ballotPrepQuestions}},mutations:{setBallotPrepQuestions:function(e,t){e.ballotPrepQuestions=t}},actions:{}},Ke={state:{votingMachinePrepQuestions:{scaleQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Scale of Voting Machine Preparation",sectionId:1,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{jurisdictionOrState:{question:"Is the preparation done at the Jurisdiction or State level?",options:["Jurisdiction","State"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"jurisdictionOrState"},scale:{question:"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.",options:["High","Medium","Low"],type:"dropdown",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"scale",tooltip:"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},accessQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Access to Voting Machine Preparation System",sectionId:2,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{remoteAccess:{question:"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"remoteAccess"},remoteAccessNoAuth:{question:"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"remoteAccessNoAuth",mitigation:null,tooltip:"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},anyIPS:{question:"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"anyIPS",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System",service:"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B",tooltip:"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity."},allowList:{question:"Do you add IPs to the 'Allow List'?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"allowList",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses",service:"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy",source:"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf",tooltip:"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses."},machineProgramming:{question:"Is the voting machine programmed through an external network? (e.g. Virtual Private Network (VPN), Internet, etc)",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"machineProgramming",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,service:null,source:null},proximateAccess:{question:"Is there proximate access to the system?",tooltip:"Proximate access refers to 'Bluetooth' and 'Wifi'.",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"proximateAccess"},bluetooth:{question:"Is Bluetooth enabled?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"bluetooth",mitigation:null,tooltip:null},wifi:{question:"Is there WiFi access?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wifi",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,tooltip:null},wepOrWpa1:{question:"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wepOrWpa1",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks."},wpa2:{question:"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wpa2",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP."},physicalMedia:{question:"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"physicalMedia"},removableMediaPolicy:{question:"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"removableMediaPolicy",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Enact removable media policy",service:"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf",tooltip:"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question."}}},authQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Authentication",sectionId:3,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{anyAuth:{question:"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"anyAuth",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},sfa:{question:"Do you use single factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"sfa",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},mfa:{question:"Do you use multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"mfa"},tfa:{question:"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"tfa",mitigation:"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet",source:"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf",tooltip:"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”."},ofa:{question:"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"ofa",mitigation:null,tooltip:"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator"}}},hardwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Hardware Management",sectionId:4,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.",questions:{patchHardware:{question:"Do you patch the server or system used to prepare voting machines?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"patchHardware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null},patchHardwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the server or system prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"patchHardwareElection",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null}}},softwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Software Management",sectionId:5,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.",questions:{patchSoftware:{question:"Do you patch your application software used to prepare voting machines?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"patchSoftware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/"},patchSoftwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the software prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"patchSoftwareElection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null}}},ddosQuestions:{sectionTitle:"DDoS Protection",sectionId:6,complete:!1,tooltip:"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.",questions:{ddosProtection:{question:"Do you have DDoS when programming a ballot on a voting machine?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"ddosProtection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation",service:"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf"}}},importanceQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Importance Values",sectionId:7,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{confidentiality:{type:"slider",default:2.9,question:"Confidentiality",id:"confidentiality",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:2.9,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},integrity:{type:"slider",default:4.9,question:"Integrity",id:"integrity",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:4.9,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},availability:{type:"slider",default:3.6,question:"Availability",id:"availability",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.6,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},additionalInformation:{sectionTitle:"Additional Information",sectionId:8,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{vmpComment1:{id:"vmpComment-1",type:"text",question:"What System is used for voting machine preparation? (State or Local System) ",userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0},vmpComment2:{id:"vmpComment-2",type:"text",question:"What is the name, make, and model of the System used for voting machine preparation?",userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0}}}}},getters:{votingMachinePrepQuestions:function(e){return e.votingMachinePrepQuestions}},mutations:{setVotingMachinePrepQuestions:function(e,t){e.votingMachinePrepQuestions=t}},actions:{}},Xe={state:{votingMachineUseQuestions:{scaleQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Scale of Voting Machine Use",sectionId:1,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{networkedOrNonNetworked:{question:"Is the voting machine networked or non-networked during voting?",options:["Networked","Non-Networked"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"networkedOrNonNetworked"},jurisdictionOrState:{question:"Is the machine managed at the Jurisdiction or State level?",options:["Jurisdiction","State"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"jurisdictionOrState"},scale:{question:"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.",options:["High","Medium","Low"],type:"dropdown",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"scale",tooltip:"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},accessQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Access to Voting Machines During Use",sectionId:2,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{remoteAccess:{question:"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"remoteAccess"},remoteAccessNoAuth:{question:"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"remoteAccessNoAuth",mitigation:null,tooltip:"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},anyIPS:{question:"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"anyIPS",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System",service:"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B",tooltip:"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity."},allowList:{question:"Do you add IPs to the 'Allow List'?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"allowList",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses",service:"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy",source:"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf",tooltip:"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses."},proximateAccess:{question:"Is there proximate access to the system?",tooltip:"Proximate access refers to 'Bluetooth' and 'Wifi'.",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"proximateAccess"},bluetooth:{question:"Is Bluetooth enabled?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"bluetooth",mitigation:null,tooltip:null},wifi:{question:"Is there WiFi access?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wifi",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,tooltip:null},wepOrWpa1:{question:"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wepOrWpa1",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks."},wpa2:{question:"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wpa2",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP."},physicalMedia:{question:"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"physicalMedia"},removableMediaPolicy:{question:"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"removableMediaPolicy",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Enact removable media policy",service:"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf",tooltip:"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question."}}},authQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Authentication",sectionId:3,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{anyAuth:{question:"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"anyAuth",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},sfa:{question:"Do you use single factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"sfa",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},mfa:{question:"Do you use multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"mfa"},tfa:{question:"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"tfa",mitigation:"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet",source:"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf",tooltip:"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”."},ofa:{question:"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"ofa",mitigation:null,tooltip:"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator"}}},hardwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Hardware Management",sectionId:4,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.",questions:{patchHardware:{question:"Do you patch the voting machines?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"patchHardware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null},patchHardwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the machines prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"patchHardwareElection",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null}}},softwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Software Management",sectionId:5,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.",questions:{patchSoftware:{question:"Do you patch any specialized application software used on the voting machines?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"patchSoftware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/"},patchSoftwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the software prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"patchSoftwareElection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null}}},ddosQuestions:{sectionTitle:"DDoS Protection",sectionId:6,complete:!1,tooltip:"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.",questions:{ddosProtection:{question:"Do you have DDoS protection when uploading ballot files to a voting machine?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"ddosProtection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation",service:"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf"}}},importanceQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Importance Values",sectionId:7,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{confidentiality:{type:"slider",default:2.9,question:"Confidentiality",id:"confidentiality",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:2.9,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},integrity:{type:"slider",default:4.9,question:"Integrity",id:"integrity",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:4.9,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},availability:{type:"slider",default:3.6,question:"Availability",id:"availability",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.6,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},additionalInformation:{sectionTitle:"Additional Information",sectionId:8,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{vmuComment1:{id:"vmuComment-1",type:"text",question:"What is the make and model of the voting machines?",userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0},vmuComment2:{id:"vmuComment-2",type:"text",question:"Do the voting machines maintain a voter verified paper record?",userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0}}}}},getters:{votingMachineUseQuestions:function(e){return e.votingMachineUseQuestions}},mutations:{setVotingMachineUseQuestions:function(e,t){e.votingMachineUseQuestions=t}},actions:{}},Ze={state:{tabulationPrepQuestions:{scaleQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Scale of Tabulation Preparation",sectionId:1,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{scale:{question:"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.",options:["High","Medium","Low"],type:"dropdown",userInput:{answer:"Medium",comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"scale",tooltip:"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},accessQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Access to Tabulation Preparation System",sectionId:2,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{remoteAccess:{question:"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"remoteAccess"},remoteAccessNoAuth:{question:"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"remoteAccessNoAuth",mitigation:null,tooltip:"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},anyIPS:{question:"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"anyIPS",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System",service:"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B",tooltip:"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity."},allowList:{question:"Do you add IPs to the 'Allow List'?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"allowList",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses",service:"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy",source:"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf",tooltip:"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses."},proximateAccess:{question:"Is there proximate access to the system?",tooltip:"Proximate access refers to 'Bluetooth' and 'Wifi'.",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"proximateAccess"},bluetooth:{question:"Is Bluetooth enabled?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"bluetooth",mitigation:null,tooltip:null},wifi:{question:"Is there WiFi access?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wifi",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,tooltip:null},wepOrWpa1:{question:"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wepOrWpa1",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks."},wpa2:{question:"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wpa2",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP."},physicalMedia:{question:"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"physicalMedia"},removableMediaPolicy:{question:"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"removableMediaPolicy",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Enact removable media policy",service:"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf",tooltip:"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question."}}},authQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Authentication",sectionId:3,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{anyAuth:{question:"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"anyAuth",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},sfa:{question:"Do you use single factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"sfa",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},mfa:{question:"Do you use multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"mfa"},tfa:{question:"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"tfa",mitigation:"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet",source:"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf",tooltip:"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”."},ofa:{question:"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"ofa",mitigation:null,tooltip:"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator"}}},hardwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Hardware Management",sectionId:4,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.",questions:{patchHardware:{question:"Do you patch the server or system used to prepare tabulation devices?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"patchHardware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null},patchHardwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the server or system prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"patchHardwareElection",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null}}},softwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Software Management",sectionId:5,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.",questions:{patchSoftware:{question:"Do you patch your application software for tabulation preparation?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"patchSoftware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/"},patchSoftwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the software prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"patchSoftwareElection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null}}},ddosQuestions:{sectionTitle:"DDoS Protection",sectionId:6,complete:!1,tooltip:"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.",questions:{ddosProtection:{question:"If you network or modem results, do you have DDoS protection on your backend server?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"ddosProtection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation",service:"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf"},machineProgramming:{question:"Do you prepare tabulation equipment using an external network? (e.g. Virtual Private Network (VPN), internet, offsite warehouse connection)",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"machineProgramming",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,service:null,source:null}}},importanceQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Importance Values",sectionId:7,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{confidentiality:{type:"slider",default:2.2,question:"Confidentiality",id:"confidentiality",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:2.2,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},integrity:{type:"slider",default:4.9,question:"Integrity",id:"integrity",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:4.9,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},availability:{type:"slider",default:3.1,question:"Availability",id:"availability",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.1,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},additionalInformation:{sectionTitle:"Additional Information",sectionId:8,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{tabPrepComment1:{id:"tabPrepComment-1",type:"text",question:"What System is used for tabulation preparation? (State or Local System)",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0},tabPrepComment2:{id:"tabPrepComment-2",type:"text",question:"What is the name, make, and model of the System used for tabulation preparation?",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0}}}}},getters:{tabulationPrepQuestions:function(e){return e.tabulationPrepQuestions}},mutations:{setTabulationPrepQuestions:function(e,t){e.tabulationPrepQuestions=t}},actions:{}},et={state:{precinctTabulationQuestions:{scaleQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Scale of Precinct Tabulation",sectionId:1,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{tabulationAtPrecincts:{question:"Do you use precinct scanners or DREs that tabulate in the precincts?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"tabulationAtPrecincts",tooltip:"DRE: Direct-Recording Electronic voting machines"},networkedOrNonNetworked:{question:"Is the precinct tabulator networked (e.g., modeming) or non-networked?",options:["Networked","Non-Networked"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"networkedOrNonNetworked"},scale:{question:"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.",options:["High","Medium","Low","N/A"],type:"dropdown",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"scale",tooltip:"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},accessQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Access to Precinct Tabulation System",sectionId:2,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{remoteAccess:{question:"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"remoteAccess"},remoteAccessNoAuth:{question:"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"remoteAccessNoAuth",mitigation:null,tooltip:"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},anyIPS:{question:"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"anyIPS",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System",service:"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B",tooltip:"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity."},allowList:{question:"Do you add IPs to the 'Allow List'?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"allowList",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses",service:"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy",source:"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf",tooltip:"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses."},proximateAccess:{question:"Is there proximate access to the system?",tooltip:"Proximate access refers to 'Bluetooth' and 'Wifi'.",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"proximateAccess"},bluetooth:{question:"Is Bluetooth enabled?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"bluetooth",mitigation:null,tooltip:null},wifi:{question:"Is there WiFi access?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wifi",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,tooltip:null},wepOrWpa1:{question:"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wepOrWpa1",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks."},wpa2:{question:"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wpa2",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP."},physicalMedia:{question:"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"physicalMedia"},removableMediaPolicy:{question:"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"removableMediaPolicy",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Enact removable media policy",service:"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf",tooltip:"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question."}}},authQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Authentication",sectionId:3,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{anyAuth:{question:"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"anyAuth",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},sfa:{question:"Do you use single factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"sfa",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},mfa:{question:"Do you use multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"mfa"},tfa:{question:"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"tfa",mitigation:"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet",source:"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf",tooltip:"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”."},ofa:{question:"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"ofa",mitigation:null,tooltip:"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator"}}},hardwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Hardware Management",sectionId:4,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.",questions:{patchHardware:{question:"Do you patch the system used for precinct tabulation?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"patchHardware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null},patchHardwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the system prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"patchHardwareElection",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null}}},softwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Software Management",sectionId:5,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.",questions:{patchSoftware:{question:"Do you patch any specialized application software used for precinct tabulation?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"patchSoftware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/"},patchSoftwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the software prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"patchSoftwareElection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null}}},ddosQuestions:{sectionTitle:"DDoS Protection",sectionId:6,complete:!1,tooltip:"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.",questions:{ddosProtection:{question:"If you network or modem results, do you have DDoS protection on your backend server?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"ddosProtection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation",service:"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf"}}},importanceQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Importance Values",sectionId:7,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{confidentiality:{type:"slider",default:2.2,question:"Confidentiality",id:"confidentiality",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:2.2,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},integrity:{type:"slider",default:4.9,question:"Integrity",id:"integrity",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:4.9,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},availability:{type:"slider",default:3.1,question:"Availability",id:"availability",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.1,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},additionalInformation:{sectionTitle:"Additional Information",sectionId:8,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{precinctTabComment1:{id:"precinctTabComment-1",type:"text",question:"What is the make and model of the tabulation machines?",userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0}}}}},getters:{precinctTabulationQuestions:function(e){return e.precinctTabulationQuestions}},mutations:{setPrecinctTabulationQuestions:function(e,t){e.precinctTabulationQuestions=t}},actions:{}},tt={state:{centralTabulationQuestions:{scaleQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Scale of Central Tabulation",sectionId:1,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{networkedOrNonNetworked:{question:"Is the central tabulation system networked or non-networked?",options:["Networked","Non-Networked"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"networkedOrNonNetworked"},jurisdictionOrState:{question:"Is tabulation occurring centrally at the jurisdiction or state level?",options:["Jurisdiction","State"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"jurisdictionOrState",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},scale:{question:"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.",options:["High","Medium","Low"],type:"dropdown",show:!1,id:"scale",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},tooltip:"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},accessQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Access to Central Tabulation System and Devices",sectionId:2,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{remoteAccess:{question:"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"remoteAccess",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},remoteAccessNoAuth:{question:"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"remoteAccessNoAuth",mitigation:null,tooltip:"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},anyIPS:{question:"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"anyIPS",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System",service:"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B",tooltip:"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},allowList:{question:"Do you add IPs to the 'Allow List'?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"allowList",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses",service:"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy",source:"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf",tooltip:"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},proximateAccess:{question:"Is there proximate access to the system?",tooltip:"Proximate access refers to 'Bluetooth' and 'Wifi'.",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"proximateAccess",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},bluetooth:{question:"Is Bluetooth enabled?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"bluetooth",mitigation:null,tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wifi:{question:"Is there WiFi access?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wifi",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wepOrWpa1:{question:"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wepOrWpa1",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wpa2:{question:"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wpa2",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},physicalMedia:{question:"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"physicalMedia",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},removableMediaPolicy:{question:"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"removableMediaPolicy",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Enact removable media policy",service:"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf",tooltip:"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},authQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Authentication",sectionId:3,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{anyAuth:{question:"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"anyAuth",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},sfa:{question:"Do you use single factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"sfa",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},mfa:{question:"Do you use multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"mfa",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},tfa:{question:"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"tfa",mitigation:"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet",source:"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf",tooltip:"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},ofa:{question:"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"ofa",mitigation:null,tooltip:"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},hardwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Hardware Management",sectionId:4,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.",questions:{patchHardware:{question:"Do you patch the system used for central tabulation?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"patchHardware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},patchHardwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the system prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"patchHardwareElection",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},softwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Software Management",sectionId:5,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.",questions:{patchSoftware:{question:"Do you patch any specialized application software used for central tabulation?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"patchSoftware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},patchSoftwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the software prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"patchSoftwareElection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},ddosQuestions:{sectionTitle:"DDoS Protection",sectionId:6,complete:!1,tooltip:"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.",questions:{ddosProtection:{question:"If you network or modem results, do you have DDoS protection on your backend server?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"ddosProtection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation",service:"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},importanceQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Importance Values",sectionId:7,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{confidentiality:{type:"slider",default:2.2,question:"Confidentiality",id:"confidentiality",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:2.2,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},integrity:{type:"slider",default:4.9,question:"Integrity",id:"integrity",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:4.9,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},availability:{type:"slider",default:3.1,question:"Availability",id:"availability",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.1,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},additionalInformation:{sectionTitle:"Additional Information",sectionId:8,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{ctComment1:{id:"ctComment-1",type:"text",question:"What is the make and model of the tabulation machines?",show:!0,userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1}},ctComment2:{id:"ctComment-2",type:"text",question:"What type of output on vote count do the tabulation machines produce?",show:!0,userInput:{answer:null,bookmarked:!1}}}}}},getters:{centralTabulationQuestions:function(e){return e.centralTabulationQuestions}},mutations:{setCentralTabulationQuestions:function(e,t){e.centralTabulationQuestions=t}},actions:{}},ot={state:{aggregationQuestions:{scaleQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Scale of State Level Aggregation",sectionId:1,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{scale:{question:"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.",options:["High","Medium","Low"],type:"dropdown",show:!0,id:"scale",userInput:{answer:"High",comments:null,bookmarked:!1},tooltip:"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},accessQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Access to State Level Aggregation System",sectionId:2,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{remoteAccess:{question:"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"remoteAccess",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},remoteAccessNoAuth:{question:"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"remoteAccessNoAuth",mitigation:null,tooltip:"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},anyIPS:{question:"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"anyIPS",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System",service:"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B",tooltip:"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},allowList:{question:"Do you add IPs to the 'Allow List'?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"allowList",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses",service:"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy",source:"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf",tooltip:"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},proximateAccess:{question:"Is there proximate access to the system?",tooltip:"Proximate access refers to 'Bluetooth' and 'Wifi'.",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"proximateAccess",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},bluetooth:{question:"Is Bluetooth enabled?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"bluetooth",mitigation:null,tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wifi:{question:"Is there WiFi access?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wifi",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wepOrWpa1:{question:"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wepOrWpa1",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},wpa2:{question:"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"wpa2",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},physicalMedia:{question:"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"physicalMedia",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},removableMediaPolicy:{question:"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"removableMediaPolicy",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Enact removable media policy",service:"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf",tooltip:"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},authQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Authentication",sectionId:3,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{anyAuth:{question:"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"anyAuth",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},sfa:{question:"Do you use single factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"sfa",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},mfa:{question:"Do you use multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"mfa",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},tfa:{question:"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"tfa",mitigation:"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet",source:"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf",tooltip:"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},ofa:{question:"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"ofa",mitigation:null,tooltip:"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},hardwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Hardware Management",sectionId:4,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.",questions:{patchHardware:{question:"Do you patch the server used to aggregate votes at the State level?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",answer:null,show:!0,id:"patchHardware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},patchHardwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the server prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"patchHardwareElection",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},softwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Software Management",sectionId:5,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.",questions:{patchSoftware:{question:"Do you patch any specialized application software used for State level vote aggregation?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"patchSoftware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},patchSoftwareElection:{question:"Is it patched prior to each election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"patchSoftwareElection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null,userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},ddosQuestions:{sectionTitle:"DDoS Protection",sectionId:6,complete:!1,tooltip:"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.",questions:{ddosProtection:{question:"Do you have DDoS protection for your server?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!0,id:"ddosProtection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation",service:"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}},importanceQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Importance Values",color:"white",sectionId:7,complete:!0,comments:null,tooltip:null,questions:{confidentiality:{type:"slider",default:2.2,question:"Confidentiality",id:"confidentiality",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:2.2,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},integrity:{type:"slider",default:4.9,question:"Integrity",id:"integrity",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:4.9,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},availability:{type:"slider",default:3.1,question:"Availability",id:"availability",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:3.1,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}}}},getters:{aggregationQuestions:function(e){return e.aggregationQuestions}},mutations:{setAggregationQuestions:function(e,t){e.aggregationQuestions=t}},actions:{}},it={state:{websiteQuestions:{scaleQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Scale of Website",sectionId:1,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{scale:{question:"The scale of risk is auto-populated based on results from experts in the election community.",options:["High","Medium","Low"],type:"dropdown",userInput:{answer:"High",comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"scale",tooltip:"The scale of impact of an attack is a measure of how widespread the direct effects would be, given a successful attack on a particular component of the election system. <b>This score is auto-populated based on your answers and expertise from the election community, but may be updated if desired.</b>"}}},accessQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Access to Website Management System",sectionId:2,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{remoteAccess:{question:"Do you allow remote access to this system (e.g., through a web portal)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"remoteAccess"},remoteAccessNoAuth:{question:"Is remote access software enabled for external users (i.e., outside your domain)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",show:!1,id:"remoteAccessNoAuth",mitigation:null,tooltip:"Examples of remote access may be Remote Desktop Protocol, Citrix, or enabling access over port 80, 5000, or 3389.",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},anyIPS:{question:"Do you use any Intrusion Protection System (IPS) and/or Intrusion Detection System (IDS)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"anyIPS",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use an Intrusion Protection System and/or Intrusion Detection System",service:"ICS-CERT TIP: Targeted Cyber Intrusion Detection and Mitigation Strategies",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/tips/ICS-TIP-12-146-01B",tooltip:"Intrusion Protection System: A cybersecurity tool that monitors network traffic flows to identify malicious activity."},allowList:{question:"Do you add IPs to the 'Allow List'?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"allowList",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Start allow listing Internet Protocol (IP) addresses",service:"NIST SP 800-41: Guidelines on Firewalls and Firewall Policy",source:"https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/Legacy/SP/nistspecialpublication800-41r1.pdf",tooltip:"Adding IPs to the Allow List is a security feature that controls network access by identifying and authorizing a list of trusted Internet Protocol (IP) addresses."},proximateAccess:{question:"Is there proximate access to the system?",tooltip:"Proximate access refers to 'Bluetooth' and 'Wifi'.",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"proximateAccess"},bluetooth:{question:"Is Bluetooth enabled?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"bluetooth",mitigation:null,tooltip:null},wifi:{question:"Is there WiFi access?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wifi",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:null,tooltip:null},wepOrWpa1:{question:"Do you use either WEP or WPA1?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wepOrWpa1",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA: Wifi-Protected Access (WPA) is a security protocol for wireless networks that replaced WEP, but has now be supplanted by WPA2. WEP:  Wired-Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is a largely outdated security protocol for wireless networks."},wpa2:{question:"Do you use either WPA2 or WPA3?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"wpa2",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use better encryption (WPA2)",service:"US-CERT: A Guide to Securing Networks for Wi-Fi",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/A_Guide_to_Securing_Networks_for_Wi-Fi.pdf",tooltip:"WPA2: Wifi-Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is an encryption protocol that helps to secure wireless networks and is a replacement for WPA and WEP."},physicalMedia:{question:"Do you allow physical access to this system (e.g., removable media)?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"physicalMedia"},removableMediaPolicy:{question:"Do you have a policy for managing removable media?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"removableMediaPolicy",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Enact removable media policy",service:"US-CERT: The Risks of Using Portable Devices",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/RisksOfPortableDevices.pdf",tooltip:"Removable media:  A portable medium of data storage that can be added or removed from a computer device or network.  Some examples include thumb drives, memory cards, and disks. A removable media policy in this situation is a security control that prevents use of unauthorized removable media such as a USB or CD-ROM. If you have a written policy that advises against using such media, but does not enforce the prohibition at the network or device level, you should answer “no” to this question."}}},authQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Authentication",sectionId:3,complete:!1,tooltip:null,questions:{anyAuth:{question:"Do you require authentication for a user to access the system?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"anyAuth",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},sfa:{question:"Do you use single factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"sfa",mitigation:"Use multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"US-CERT Alert TA18-276A: Using Rigorous Credential Control to Mitigate Trusted Network Exploitation",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/ncas/alerts/TA18-276A"},mfa:{question:"Do you use multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"mfa"},tfa:{question:"Do you use a text message (or email) for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"tfa",mitigation:"Use physical objects for multi-factor authentication (MFA)",service:"DHS Multi-Factor Authentication Quick Sheet",source:"https://www.dhs.gov/sites/default/files/publications/19_0419_cisa-multi-factor-authentication.pdf",tooltip:"If you’re using an app-based system or Google Authenticator, your answer should be “No”."},ofa:{question:"Do you use a physical object for your multi-factor authentication?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"ofa",mitigation:null,tooltip:"PIV Card, Yubikey, or app-based system such as Google Authenticator"}}},hardwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Hardware Management",sectionId:4,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, hardware is taken to mean the physical devices or systems as delivered by the original manufacturer. This includes all system software, such as operating systems.",questions:{patchHardware:{question:"Do you patch the server used to host your website?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"patchHardware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null},patchHardwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the server more frequently than once per election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,showMitigation:!1,id:"patchHardwareElection",mitigation:"Patch server regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null}}},softwareQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Software Management",sectionId:5,complete:!1,tooltip:"Here, software is taken to mean any specialized applications which were not delivered with the system hardware. This may include applications such as Elections Management Systems.",questions:{patchSoftware:{question:"Do you patch any specialized application software used to manage your website?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"patchSoftware",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/"},patchSoftwareElection:{question:"Do you patch the software more frequently than once per election?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!1,id:"patchSoftwareElection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Patch software regularly",service:"DHS Binding Operational Directive 19-02: Vulnerability Remediation Requirements for Internet-Accessible Systems",source:"https://cyber.dhs.gov/bod/19-02/",tooltip:null}}},ddosQuestions:{sectionTitle:"DDoS Protection",sectionId:6,complete:!1,tooltip:"DDoS Protection: Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection is a set of tools and services that mitigate the consequences of DDoS attacks.",questions:{ddosProtection:{question:"Do you have DDoS protection for your server?",options:["Yes","No"],type:"radio",userInput:{answer:null,comments:null,bookmarked:!1},show:!0,id:"ddosProtection",showMitigation:!1,mitigation:"Implement DDoS protection during ballot preparation",service:"US-CERT: DDoS Quick Guide",source:"https://www.us-cert.gov/sites/default/files/publications/DDoS%20Quick%20Guide.pdf"}}},importanceQuestions:{sectionTitle:"Importance Values",sectionId:7,complete:!0,tooltip:null,questions:{confidentiality:{type:"slider",default:1.5,question:"Confidentiality",id:"confidentiality",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:1.5,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},integrity:{type:"slider",default:4.3,question:"Integrity",id:"integrity",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:4.3,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}},availability:{type:"slider",default:2.1,question:"Availability",id:"availability",show:!0,userInput:{userValue:2.1,comments:null,bookmarked:!1}}}}}},getters:{websiteQuestions:function(e){return e.websiteQuestions}},mutations:{setWebsiteQuestions:function(e,t){e.websiteQuestions=t}},actions:{}},st={state:{surveyTabs:{1:{name:"Voter Registration",step:1,hideStep:!1},2:{name:"Pollbook Preparation",step:2,hideStep:!1},3:{name:"Pollbook Use",step:3,hideStep:!1},4:{name:"Ballot Preparation",step:4,hideStep:!1},5:{name:"Voting Machine Preparation",step:5,hideStep:!1},6:{name:"Voting Machine Use",step:6,hideStep:!1},7:{name:"Tabulation Preparation",step:7,hideStep:!0},8:{name:"Tabulation Use (Precinct)",step:8,hideStep:!1},9:{name:"Tabulation Use (Central)",step:9,hideStep:!1},10:{name:"Aggregation (State)",step:10,hideStep:!1},11:{name:"Website",step:11,hideStep:!1}}},getters:{surveyTabs:function(e){return e.surveyTabs}}};i["a"].use(Fe["a"]);var nt=new Fe["a"].Store({state:{},mutations:{},actions:{},modules:{applicationControl:Be,sectionsVisited:Le,voterRegistration:Ge,pollUse:Je,pollPrep:ze,ballotPrep:$e,votingMachinePrep:Ke,votingMachineUse:Xe,tabPrep:Ze,precinctTabulation:et,centralTabulation:tt,aggregation:ot,website:it,surveySections:st}}),rt=o("f309"),at={red:"#EA3D06",orange:"#EA7006",green:"#69C109",blue:"#3751FF",grey:"#767676",black:"#000000",white:"#FFFFFF",light:{lightestBlue:"F5F6FF",blue:"#929EF1",grey:"#C8C8C8"},dark:{blue:"#1B283B"}};i["a"].use(rt["a"]);var lt=new rt["a"]({icons:{iconfont:"mdi",values:{chevdown:"mdi-chevron-down"}},theme:{options:{customProperties:!1},themes:{light:{primary:at.dark.blue,anchor:at.light.grey,secondary:at.blue,accent:at.light.grey,error:at.red,lightestBlue:at.light.lightestBlue,lightBlue:at.light.blue,blue:at.blue,grey:at.light.grey,darkGrey:at.grey,danger:at.red},dark:{primary:at.blue,anchor:at.blue,secondary:at.grey,error:at.red}}}});o("b339");i["a"].config.productionTip=!1,new i["a"]({router:Oe,store:nt,vuetify:lt,render:function(e){return e(ye)}}).$mount("#app")},d63f:function(e,t,o){},d681:function(e,t,o){},dfa3:function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.d(t,"a",(function(){return s}));var i=o("2b0e"),s=new i["a"]},e162:function(e,t,o){e.exports=o.p+"img/home-upload.a83b8bc5.svg"},fe4d:function(e,t,o){}});
//# sourceMappingURL=app.8cf504c6.js.map